<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>/r/mcp/.rss</id>
  <title>Model Context Protocol (MCP)</title>
  <updated>2026-01-13T19:24:38+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/" rel="alternate"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <icon>https://www.redditstatic.com/icon.png/</icon>
  <subtitle>The Model Context Protocol is an open standard that enables developers to build secure, two-way connections between their data sources and AI-powered tools</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbjn9z</id>
    <title>MCP Elicitation - Hardest functionality of MCP Development</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T06:03:20+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/hasmcp</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/hasmcp</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you are building elicitation based on URL and FORM, the challenge is the similar how are you going to intercept the request and get input and continue. I will share my experience with URL based one, would love to hear your thoughts. The URL based elicitation has more clear direction it offers 2 options:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Opt1: Reactive&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Raise error on the JSONRPC response (this is the one I technically prefer, will share the reason later). When the server needs more input to perform a tool execution, MCP Host gets error with specific code &lt;strong&gt;URLElicitationRequiredError&lt;/strong&gt; and display the URL to the user. So, the user will click this provided session specific URL and add necessary inputs and once the MCP Server gets correct inputs then it sends notification to the MCP client.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Opt2: Proactive&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this scenario, server initiates the elicitation request with or without any ask from the client. It is like I provided all tools, prompts, resources but I need something else from you before doing anything else. MCP server send notification to the client with URL then client display the URL to the user. User continues with URL and complete the task. The task could be like authenticate with underlying provider or provide your name in an external form input.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But why I prefer reactive over proactive one in most scenario; it is all about user's session security, I don't want to get all tool permissions or all inputs if they are not needed at all. I don't know fully user's intent, maybe they just loaded the server but don't want to perform anything at all. I am sure there a lot of legit use-case. One of them is not to bother user multiple times with different permission asks. But isn't it the safety of the user at all? I would love to hear from you to learn in the thread.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What is hard?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is stateful by the spec definition. Session management, keeping this information per session based actually per elicitation identifier based is most challenging part. As part of the critical responsibility of storing this information as a developer we should be responsibly encrypt and decrypt when we need to use these values. Especially if you are building a multi-tenant MCP server, things become harder.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Steps I applied on HasMCP:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1) On initialize method call: Generate unique session id (MCP-Session-Id) give it to the mcp client as jwt token. It includes a unique internal session id, limited OAuth2 scopes and client capabilities to allow interacting mcp gateway with a specific server. This saved me a lot of time to burden from cold starts. If somehow server or the underlying session db dies, I know everything I need from this jwt token to authorize and store it back as session.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2) On a tool call check the required scopes (first call)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3) Check if the client supports elicitation (from client capabilities) -&amp;gt; if not let it fail&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4) Create OAuth2 authorize url for the actual provider like for Google and return URLElicitationRequiredError with this URL&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This 4th step is critical; While generating the OAuth2 state value, Adding elicitation id, server id, session id information retrievable from this state.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5) User clicks the link if the LLM smart enough it display the url even sometimes button&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6) On OAuth2 callback I store the values to the session (access token with scopes, refresh token [both encrypted])&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;7) Redirect user to close window that says elicitation successful&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;8) User tries again on the MCP Host&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;9) Successful attempt for the user&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Next tool call from the client:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;11) Check if the existing token is not expired and has scopes&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;12) Yes then just use the access token&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- What is the challenge? Session recovery, session storage, multi-tenancy, allowing public MCPs without user accounts&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- How would be easier? If it would not need to support public MCPs. I could only need to store into user. But a customer ask was to expose their MCPs using a single user account and sponsor the MCP calls. Like saying my product MCP URL is xyz and I would like to allow my users to use it without being member to your platform. They should login with our own OAuth2 login.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Based on the feedbacks on upcoming weeks, I might switch to full scopes but wanted to start strict for ensuring not getting unnecessary scopes. I will listen the customers and share updates. You can decide if the elicitation is hard or the public multi-tenant MCPs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This post is 100% handwritten, no AI/LLM inputs are taken. Published also in substack!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/hasmcp"&gt; /u/hasmcp &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbjn9z/mcp_elicitation_hardest_functionality_of_mcp/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbjn9z/mcp_elicitation_hardest_functionality_of_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbjn9z/mcp_elicitation_hardest_functionality_of_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T06:03:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbprow</id>
    <title>Unofficial MCP take down</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T12:14:41+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Triple-Tooketh</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Triple-Tooketh</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quick question, has anyone posted an unofficial MCP server and then received a take down notice? Is Unofficial kind of an accepted practice? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Triple-Tooketh"&gt; /u/Triple-Tooketh &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbprow/unofficial_mcp_take_down/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbprow/unofficial_mcp_take_down/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbprow/unofficial_mcp_take_down/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T12:14:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbnhc4</id>
    <title>Context7 Quietly Slashed Its Free Tier by 92%</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T10:01:08+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/jpcaparas</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/jpcaparas</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The popular MCP server now limits free users to 500 requests per month&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/jpcaparas"&gt; /u/jpcaparas &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://jpcaparas.medium.com/context7-quietly-slashed-its-free-tier-by-92-16fa05ddce03"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbnhc4/context7_quietly_slashed_its_free_tier_by_92/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbnhc4/context7_quietly_slashed_its_free_tier_by_92/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T10:01:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbsa7l</id>
    <title>Which MCP server did you find useful for Data analysis?</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T14:09:50+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Dazzling_Basil_4739</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Dazzling_Basil_4739</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello people!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I've been thinking of using an open-source MCP server to make my tasks easier like data analysis. I would like to know which open-source MCP server(s) worked well for you in this regard.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Dazzling_Basil_4739"&gt; /u/Dazzling_Basil_4739 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbsa7l/which_mcp_server_did_you_find_useful_for_data/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbsa7l/which_mcp_server_did_you_find_useful_for_data/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbsa7l/which_mcp_server_did_you_find_useful_for_data/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T14:09:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbuyba</id>
    <title>I built an AI that reads SEC filings so you don’t have to. Roasts welcome.</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T15:53:46+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/finance-mcp-001</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/finance-mcp-001</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people ignore qualitative SEC disclosures… but they’re insanely valuable.&lt;br /&gt; So I built a tool that lets you ask &lt;em&gt;any finance question&lt;/em&gt; and it answers strictly using SEC filings (no made-up nonsense). Check it out: &lt;a href="https://www.askbach.com"&gt;https://www.askbach.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Examples it handles:&lt;br /&gt; • “What did Tesla say about the risks it faces? How does this compare to last year?”&lt;br /&gt; • “How does Microsoft vs. Apple talk about tariffs?”&lt;br /&gt; • “What companies are at risk of bankruptcy?”&lt;br /&gt; • “Compare Nvidia's vs. Oracle's main financials.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I want honest feedback:&lt;br /&gt; – Would you use this?&lt;br /&gt; – What’s missing?&lt;br /&gt; – What would make it &lt;em&gt;10x&lt;/em&gt; more useful?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hit me with feature ideas / criticisms / killer use-cases. I’ll listen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/finance-mcp-001"&gt; /u/finance-mcp-001 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbuyba/i_built_an_ai_that_reads_sec_filings_so_you_dont/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbuyba/i_built_an_ai_that_reads_sec_filings_so_you_dont/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbuyba/i_built_an_ai_that_reads_sec_filings_so_you_dont/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T15:53:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbvrnt</id>
    <title>Creating a basic MCP server (walkthrough with repo)</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T16:23:44+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Ok_Message7136</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Ok_Message7136</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbvrnt/creating_a_basic_mcp_server_walkthrough_with_repo/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Creating a basic MCP server (walkthrough with repo)" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/dTZyaDJjN3g2NWRnMTc0WkxhYYAFW8xBOj2JZx4-ydWzGuSiO9K3aXQQS6kv.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=3a769347028cf7b2bf4bae3d1ca6a9a4f8854742" title="Creating a basic MCP server (walkthrough with repo)" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you can build your own MCP server &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This resource covers:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Creating an MCP server from scratch&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Minimal MCP flow&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Core concepts in practice&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Repo: &lt;a href="https://github.com/GopherSecurity/gopher-mcp"&gt;https://github.com/GopherSecurity/gopher-mcp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Ok_Message7136"&gt; /u/Ok_Message7136 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://v.redd.it/g44ppu6x65dg1"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbvrnt/creating_a_basic_mcp_server_walkthrough_with_repo/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbvrnt/creating_a_basic_mcp_server_walkthrough_with_repo/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T16:23:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qarjqm</id>
    <title>5 MCPs that have genuinely made me 10x faster</title>
    <updated>2026-01-12T10:34:54+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/ScratchAshamed593</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/ScratchAshamed593</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using MCPs extensively at work, so I thought I’d share some of the ones I’ve found most useful.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My main criteria were minimal setup, reliability, and whether I kept using them after the novelty wore off:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Context7 MCP: (Documentation and knowledge)This is by far the best MCP I’ve used for coding. It helps your agents fetch the latest documentation automatically. For me, I used to ask the agent to implement a feature X from Y technology and I have never had to deal with documentation.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Firecrawl MCP / Jina Reader MCP: These are good for turning URLs into clean Markdown. They strip boilerplate, nav, and ads so the agent can focus on the actual article, although very interactive apps or paywalled content may still require a manual check.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Figma MCP: (Design and UI) Design-to-code is the basic necessity nowadays for frontend development. This MCP server exposes the live structure of the layer you have selected in Figma, which includes hierarchy, auto‑layout, variants, text styles, and token references. Tools like Claude, Cursor, or Windsurf can use it to generate code against real designs instead of screenshots.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Slack / Messaging MCP: High “aha” factor with very low effort. Once an agent can talk where humans already are, teams love it instantly. My team even used this for something as basic as ordering and tracking deliveries for team lunch, which ended up being one of the most-used workflows for us.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;GitHub MCP: This is what finally made Claude feel like an actual teammate instead of a smarter autocomplete. If you’re tired of copy-pasting repos into prompts, you’re gonna love it. It’s especially helpful for issue + commit context grounding and repo exploration.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;Super curious to hear what MCPs all of you have found useful?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/ScratchAshamed593"&gt; /u/ScratchAshamed593 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qarjqm/5_mcps_that_have_genuinely_made_me_10x_faster/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qarjqm/5_mcps_that_have_genuinely_made_me_10x_faster/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qarjqm/5_mcps_that_have_genuinely_made_me_10x_faster/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-12T10:34:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbwim3</id>
    <title>I Tried an MCP, But Did It Really Help Me Get Work Done?</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T16:50:54+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Dazzling_Basil_4739</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Dazzling_Basil_4739</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, I was experimenting with an MCP platform, trying to automate some of my daily work. I got it to connect a few tools, move some data around, and even generate reports. But at the end of the day, I stopped and asked myself: Did this really make my work easier, or was I just impressed by what it could do?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It got me thinking that most MCP demos focus on capabilities. “Look, it can connect 2000 tools! Look, it can run multiple actions at once!” That’s cool, but I’m curious about the real outcomes. Are these tools saving time? Reducing mistakes? Helping people actually get work done they couldn’t before?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But maybe that’s not what most people want. I want to know how you use an MCP server and what you actually want from it. Is it about connecting more tools, automating specific workflows, helping with data, reducing context switching, or something else entirely?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Dazzling_Basil_4739"&gt; /u/Dazzling_Basil_4739 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbwim3/i_tried_an_mcp_but_did_it_really_help_me_get_work/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbwim3/i_tried_an_mcp_but_did_it_really_help_me_get_work/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbwim3/i_tried_an_mcp_but_did_it_really_help_me_get_work/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T16:50:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbx4j1</id>
    <title>Langchain vs Native Remote MCP integration?</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T17:21:15+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Much-Whole-8611</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Much-Whole-8611</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am developing an agentic product and we've been using Langchain so far to create an agent that can interact with a remote MCP server.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We hate all the abstractions so far and the fact that langchain makes 1 million extra calls to the API providers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Has anyone here used the native MCP integration with OpenAI's new Responses API or Gemini's Interactions API?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Is it good? Is it interpretable or does everything happen on their servers and black-box?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It seems like a MUCH cleaner &amp;amp; more performant approach than using Langchain.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Much-Whole-8611"&gt; /u/Much-Whole-8611 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbx4j1/langchain_vs_native_remote_mcp_integration/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbx4j1/langchain_vs_native_remote_mcp_integration/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbx4j1/langchain_vs_native_remote_mcp_integration/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T17:21:15+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbx9ed</id>
    <title>FastMCP does not play along with local models on Openwebui</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T17:25:58+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/GliklekhMentsh</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/GliklekhMentsh</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I cannot make a local simple fastmcp server work with openwebui using a local LLM , openwebui always returns &amp;quot;cannot pickle '_asyncio.Future'&lt;br /&gt; object&amp;quot; .... remote openapi models do work and returns data correctly ... &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;mc works fine with mcp inspector &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Any known issue ? solution ? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/GliklekhMentsh"&gt; /u/GliklekhMentsh &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbx9ed/fastmcp_does_not_play_along_with_local_models_on/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbx9ed/fastmcp_does_not_play_along_with_local_models_on/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbx9ed/fastmcp_does_not_play_along_with_local_models_on/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T17:25:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbmn6p</id>
    <title>Jira MCP - Better than ever</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T09:07:41+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/EcstaticDiscussion32</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/EcstaticDiscussion32</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Saw the emerging wave of improving official MCPs, and wanted to give it a try.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I've developed a Jira MCP - more efficient, less tools, focuses only on what matters.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The most important part is the local hosting. I don't trust remote servers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Give it a try, and don't hesitate to give the repo a star!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/Jira-MCP/Jira-MCP"&gt;https://github.com/Jira-MCP/Jira-MCP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/EcstaticDiscussion32"&gt; /u/EcstaticDiscussion32 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbmn6p/jira_mcp_better_than_ever/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbmn6p/jira_mcp_better_than_ever/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbmn6p/jira_mcp_better_than_ever/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T09:07:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qb7bx7</id>
    <title>Anyone else find mcp setup to be a massive pain?</title>
    <updated>2026-01-12T21:09:03+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Apprehensive_Ice9370</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Apprehensive_Ice9370</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently introduced to MCP thinking the hard part would be getting a server running, but I was surprised that that was the easy bit.. the pain started when I tried to make it usable in practice like custom server logic, proper auth and permissions, logging and analytics.. to understand what the agent is doing, and then figuring out how to host it safely without creating a security mess&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wanted to connect Postgres and some internal docs to Claude Desktop, but turning that into something I’d be comfortable running for more than a demo took way longer than expected.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I needed to find a tool mostly out of fatigue, and it helped with a lot of the plumbing (especially auth, logging, and hosting), but I’m curious how others are handling this (ogment ai, in case anyone else is using it). Are people rolling their own production MCP servers, or is there a better pattern I’m missing?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Apprehensive_Ice9370"&gt; /u/Apprehensive_Ice9370 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qb7bx7/anyone_else_find_mcp_setup_to_be_a_massive_pain/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qb7bx7/anyone_else_find_mcp_setup_to_be_a_massive_pain/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qb7bx7/anyone_else_find_mcp_setup_to_be_a_massive_pain/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-12T21:09:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbyxzn</id>
    <title>Spreadsheet MCP - High performance &amp; token-efficient Excel tools for LLM agents (read, write, execute, screenshot)</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T18:25:09+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Manfr3dMacx</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Manfr3dMacx</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dumping a 50k-row spreadsheet into an LLM context is expensive and usually unnecessary. Most tasks need surgical access ie: find a region, profile its structure, read a filtered slice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;SpreadsheetMCP is a Rust MCP server with 20+ tools that let agents discover -&amp;gt; profile -&amp;gt; extract without burning tokens on cells they don't need. Supports xlsx/xlsm, VBA inspection, formula tracing, what-if analysis via forks, and headless screenshots via LibreOffice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Manfr3dMacx"&gt; /u/Manfr3dMacx &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/PSU3D0/spreadsheet-mcp"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbyxzn/spreadsheet_mcp_high_performance_tokenefficient/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbyxzn/spreadsheet_mcp_high_performance_tokenefficient/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T18:25:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbz2xb</id>
    <title>Examples of a client that implements Tasks spec?</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T18:29:57+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking to find examples of clients that implement the &lt;a href="https://modelcontextprotocol.io/specification/2025-11-25/basic/utilities/tasks"&gt;tasks spec&lt;/a&gt;. I know of a few inspectors/playgrounds that implement them, but looking for actual clients that are meant to be used on daily basis.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbz2xb/examples_of_a_client_that_implements_tasks_spec/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbz2xb/examples_of_a_client_that_implements_tasks_spec/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbz2xb/examples_of_a_client_that_implements_tasks_spec/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T18:29:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbtjf6</id>
    <title>OpenAlex Research MCP Server – Provides access to OpenAlex's catalog of 240+ million scholarly works through 18 specialized tools for conducting literature reviews, analyzing citations, tracking research trends, and mapping the scholarly landscape including authors, institutions, and collaboration n</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T15:00:12+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/modelcontextprotocol</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/modelcontextprotocol</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbtjf6/openalex_research_mcp_server_provides_access_to/"&gt; &lt;img alt="OpenAlex Research MCP Server – Provides access to OpenAlex's catalog of 240+ million scholarly works through 18 specialized tools for conducting literature reviews, analyzing citations, tracking research trends, and mapping the scholarly landscape including authors, institutions, and collaboration n" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/7T4buoJbcV8m_3zC4rwKczjTf2GQoBWiRTSP2F67lvs.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=383f10660be0c03195c43bab8ffe5416bc56264f" title="OpenAlex Research MCP Server – Provides access to OpenAlex's catalog of 240+ million scholarly works through 18 specialized tools for conducting literature reviews, analyzing citations, tracking research trends, and mapping the scholarly landscape including authors, institutions, and collaboration n" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/modelcontextprotocol"&gt; /u/modelcontextprotocol &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://glama.ai/mcp/servers/@oksure/openalex-research-mcp"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbtjf6/openalex_research_mcp_server_provides_access_to/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbtjf6/openalex_research_mcp_server_provides_access_to/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T15:00:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qc05fs</id>
    <title>Agent Debugging Feels Primitive</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T19:07:48+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Upstairs_Safe2922</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Upstairs_Safe2922</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been having issues with agent debugging. Feels like the context I get is limited at best. I check logs and see: tool_call:xyz. Without much insight into WHY it happened. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I'm most worried about is what happens in the runtime post tool call. Any thoughts/suggestions?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Upstairs_Safe2922"&gt; /u/Upstairs_Safe2922 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qc05fs/agent_debugging_feels_primitive/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qc05fs/agent_debugging_feels_primitive/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qc05fs/agent_debugging_feels_primitive/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T19:07:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qc0m11</id>
    <title>Code Mode in Bifrost cuts MCP token usage in half - here's how it works</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T19:24:26+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/dinkinflika0</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/dinkinflika0</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclosure: I help maintain Bifrost and we wanted to share Code Mode since it's been a game changer for MCP workflows.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The problem&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; When you connect multiple MCP servers (filesystem, web search, databases), you end up exposing hundreds of tool definitions to the LLM. Token usage explodes, latency increases, and the model gets overwhelmed with options.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Code Mode approach&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Instead of exposing all tools individually, the LLM writes TypeScript code that orchestrates multiple tools. Code executes in a Goja VM sandbox with type-safe bindings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Code is open source if you want to see the implementation: &lt;a href="https://github.com/maxim-ai/bifrost"&gt;https://github.com/maxim-ai/bifrost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Generate .d.ts declarations for all MCP tools&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;LLM writes TypeScript to orchestrate workflow&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Code transpiles and runs in sandboxed VM&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Single LLM call instead of multiple round-trips&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance impact:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Token usage drops by over half (no massive tool lists in context)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Latency reduced significantly (single LLM call vs iterative loop)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Handles complex workflows with conditionals, loops, error handling&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example:&lt;/strong&gt; Instead of calling &lt;code&gt;list_directory&lt;/code&gt;, then &lt;code&gt;read_file&lt;/code&gt; for each result, then &lt;code&gt;write_file&lt;/code&gt; with processed content (multiple LLM round-trips), the model writes code that does all three in sequence.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security constraints:&lt;/strong&gt; Sandboxed execution - no Node.js APIs, no network access, no filesystem access outside MCP tools. Console output captured. Execution timeout enforced.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/dinkinflika0"&gt; /u/dinkinflika0 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qc0m11/code_mode_in_bifrost_cuts_mcp_token_usage_in_half/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qc0m11/code_mode_in_bifrost_cuts_mcp_token_usage_in_half/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qc0m11/code_mode_in_bifrost_cuts_mcp_token_usage_in_half/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T19:24:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbwcuq</id>
    <title>Consolidated 195 tools down to 28 using action enums</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T16:44:56+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Low-Efficiency-9756</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Low-Efficiency-9756</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working on an RPG MCP server, we hit a scaling problem: every CRUD operation for every entity got its own tool. Characters alone had `create_character`, `get_character`, `update_character`, `delete_character`, `list_characters`. Multiply that across items, quests, combat, parties, etc. and we ended up with 195 tools and ~50k tokens of schema definitions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The fix was simple. Instead of separate tools per operation, we made domain tools with an `action` enum:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;create_character&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;get_character&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;update_character&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;delete_character&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;list_characters&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;character_manage(action: &amp;quot;create&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;get&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;update&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;delete&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;list&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;search&amp;quot;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Applied across the board, this dropped us to 28 tools and ~6-8k tokens of schema. Same functionality, 85% less overhead.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We also added fuzzy matching on action values so typos get helpful suggestions instead of opaque failures.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you’re building MCP servers and your tool count is ballooning, action enums might be worth considering. Happy to answer questions about the implementation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Low-Efficiency-9756"&gt; /u/Low-Efficiency-9756 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbwcuq/consolidated_195_tools_down_to_28_using_action/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbwcuq/consolidated_195_tools_down_to_28_using_action/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbwcuq/consolidated_195_tools_down_to_28_using_action/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T16:44:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbxuli</id>
    <title>A2A MCP server, an MCP server for the A2A protocol!</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T17:46:43+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/benclarkereddit</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/benclarkereddit</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbxuli/a2a_mcp_server_an_mcp_server_for_the_a2a_protocol/"&gt; &lt;img alt="A2A MCP server, an MCP server for the A2A protocol!" src="https://preview.redd.it/nufkq188m5dg1.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d437ba8dc24afa9dc461f415db0639c2a5ff4d41" title="A2A MCP server, an MCP server for the A2A protocol!" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the past month I’ve been working on an &lt;a href="https://github.com/a2anet/a2a-mcp"&gt;A2A MCP server&lt;/a&gt;. The server can be used to connect and send messages to A2A Servers (remote agents).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The server needs to be initialised with one or more Agent Card URLs, each of which can have custom headers for authentication, configuration, etc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Agents and their skills can be viewed with the &lt;code&gt;list_available_agents&lt;/code&gt; tool, messages can be sent to the agents with the &lt;code&gt;send_message_to_agent&lt;/code&gt; tool, and Artifacts that would overload the context can be viewed with &lt;code&gt;view_text_artifact&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;view_data_artifact&lt;/code&gt; tools.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For a full list of features, quick start, and examples, check out the GitHub link above!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/benclarkereddit"&gt; /u/benclarkereddit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.redd.it/nufkq188m5dg1.png"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbxuli/a2a_mcp_server_an_mcp_server_for_the_a2a_protocol/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbxuli/a2a_mcp_server_an_mcp_server_for_the_a2a_protocol/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T17:46:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbz7ho</id>
    <title>Browser control with a CLI vs MCP</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T18:34:22+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/sean-adapt</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/sean-adapt</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/sean-adapt"&gt; /u/sean-adapt &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="/r/nextjs/comments/1qbz5sf/vercels_agentbrowser_an_alternative_to/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbz7ho/browser_control_with_a_cli_vs_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbz7ho/browser_control_with_a_cli_vs_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T18:34:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbzdhz</id>
    <title>MCPs are a workaround</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T18:40:19+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Accomplished-Emu8030</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Accomplished-Emu8030</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll see posts saying “MCPs are a fad,” and other posts saying “MCPs are amazing.” I think both sides are missing the point.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;MCPs exist because they’re solving a very real pain &lt;em&gt;right now&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When Anthropic shipped MCP, the intent was clear: make it easier for models to plug into real systems. The “USB-C for AI tools” line was great marketing, but the deeper truth is simpler: MCP fit their product constraints and made integrations safer and more repeatable.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then adoption took off and a narrative formed: “This is the new wave.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But I don’t think teams adopted MCP because everyone concluded it’s the One True Interface. Adoption happened because lots of teams hit the same wall at the same time: &lt;strong&gt;LLMs weren’t reliable enough to write integration code live without messing it up.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In theory, if a model could generate perfect code every time, you wouldn’t need MCP. The model could just generate whatever connector you need on the spot and it would work. But that wasn’t the world we were living in. Models could code, sure—but “pretty good” isn’t good enough when you’re dealing with production systems, permissions, and actions that move money.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fast-forward to now: models are meaningfully better at code. And you can see the product direction shifting with that reality. Anthropic started talking about &lt;em&gt;code-based tool calling&lt;/em&gt;—roughly: “what if tools are scripts (real code) instead of only protocol-shaped endpoints?” That arc naturally leads into things like Skills.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That’s the part I find most interesting: &lt;em&gt;tooling evolves with model capability.&lt;/em&gt; MCP made sense when models needed tighter guardrails. Code-first approaches make more sense as models get stronger.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And all this brings me to what we’re releasing today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We’re releasing a framework called &lt;a href="https://github.com/brwse/operai"&gt;Operai&lt;/a&gt; (operations + AI, and yes, a nod to operads). Call it a plug if you want—it's public and we think it’s the better direction for the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our main thesis is: Instead of orchestrating agents + a giant pile of tools, &lt;em&gt;orchestrate tools with policies&lt;/em&gt; and keep the tool surface area &lt;em&gt;small, scoped, and deliberate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A dedicated toolset beats a Swiss Army knife.&lt;/em&gt; You can fumble around with a “do-everything” MCP, or you can just program a tool that does the job—cleanly, predictably, and safely.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Policy orchestration matters more than agent orchestration.&lt;/em&gt; In a real org, leadership doesn’t micromanage every person’s steps. They define constraints: approval rules, audit requirements, budgets, access boundaries. When you “orchestrate agents,” you’re implicitly trying to micromanage. You shouldn’t care about the agent’s personality—you should care about &lt;strong&gt;what it is allowed to do&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Operai uses an &lt;em&gt;effect-based policy system&lt;/em&gt;: agents can behave flexibly, but the system enforces guardrails on side effects. The policies protect the endgame.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The workflow with operai is simple:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Create a Git repo that stores your tools.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Build tools with your favorite coding assistant + the Operai CLI.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Serve them with Operai.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;Under the hood we made choices that are biased toward enterprise reality and how LLMs actually behave. For example, we chose Rust because Python/JS don’t give you compile-time guarantees—and when you’re exposing capabilities to an agent, you want as many guarantees as you can get.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do we think this is where things go?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Because programs aren’t going away. Even with infinite context, we’re not “hedging probability” here—we’re enforcing logic: access control, schemas, invariants, side effects, logging, auditing. Those aren’t optional. The transport is secondary. What we need is a solid mechanism for AI to generate &lt;strong&gt;good&lt;/strong&gt; programs—not ad-hoc scripts, not unaudited glue code, but real software: versioned, typed, testable, reviewable, observable. The kind of quality level you’d expect from something like ripgrep.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So our bet is simple:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The future isn’t picking a single protocol and arguing forever. It’s treating tools like real software—whether it's fully authored by a human or an AI—without pretending the model is perfect.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Accomplished-Emu8030"&gt; /u/Accomplished-Emu8030 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbzdhz/mcps_are_a_workaround/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbzdhz/mcps_are_a_workaround/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbzdhz/mcps_are_a_workaround/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T18:40:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qbpofz</id>
    <title>Mapped the agent infrastructure stack - where MCP fits relative to A2A, ACP, UCP, and the payment protocols</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T12:09:59+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/PutPurple844</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/PutPurple844</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notion Doc: &lt;a href="https://agentic-ecosystem-daily.notion.site/Agentic-Ecosystem-Research-2e4ff2f808c381fab03adbe8d4b168f1"&gt;https://agentic-ecosystem-daily.notion.site/Agentic-Ecosystem-Research-2e4ff2f808c381fab03adbe8d4b168f1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Been tracking how the ecosystem around MCP is evolving. Here's how I'm seeing the layers:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Commerce: ACP (OpenAI) / UCP (Google) Payments: Visa TAP / Mastercard Agent Pay / x402 Agent-Agent: A2A (Google) Agent-Tool: MCP (Anthropic) &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;p&gt;Key recent stuff:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AAIF launched&lt;/strong&gt; - MCP, A2A, ACP now under Linux Foundation governance. Anthropic, OpenAI, Google, and Microsoft are all involved.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A2A explicitly &amp;quot;complements MCP&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt; - agent-to-agent vs agent-to-tool. Boundary still fuzzy.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identity unsolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Microsoft, AWS, startups all taking different approaches. No standard for MCP server auth yet.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OWASP Agentic Top 10&lt;/strong&gt; shipped in December — an actual security framework now exists.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Put together a research hub covering all the protocols, payment rails, identity approaches, and security frameworks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Keeping it updated. Curious what others are seeing - especially around MCP auth patterns and how A2A/MCP will interact in practice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/PutPurple844"&gt; /u/PutPurple844 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbpofz/mapped_the_agent_infrastructure_stack_where_mcp/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbpofz/mapped_the_agent_infrastructure_stack_where_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qbpofz/mapped_the_agent_infrastructure_stack_where_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T12:09:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1qby86x</id>
    <title>WhatsApp OSINT MCP Server – Enables querying WhatsApp OSINT API to gather intelligence on WhatsApp numbers, including business verification, user status, privacy settings, linked devices, and profile pictures.</title>
    <updated>2026-01-13T18:00:09+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/modelcontextprotocol</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/modelcontextprotocol</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qby86x/whatsapp_osint_mcp_server_enables_querying/"&gt; &lt;img alt="WhatsApp OSINT MCP Server – Enables querying WhatsApp OSINT API to gather intelligence on WhatsApp numbers, including business verification, user status, privacy settings, linked devices, and profile pictures." src="https://external-preview.redd.it/dsOdkptiF3tTqRfKT2tn6diglYVZ8EzBzgCKIMpMqsM.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=53585e686b598b0240c08d77c6c723e57c5a5d4a" title="WhatsApp OSINT MCP Server – Enables querying WhatsApp OSINT API to gather intelligence on WhatsApp numbers, including business verification, user status, privacy settings, linked devices, and profile pictures." /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/modelcontextprotocol"&gt; /u/modelcontextprotocol &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://glama.ai/mcp/servers/@BACH-AI-Tools/bachai-whatsapp-osint"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qby86x/whatsapp_osint_mcp_server_enables_querying/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1qby86x/whatsapp_osint_mcp_server_enables_querying/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2026-01-13T18:00:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1h7pl2v</id>
    <title>Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T01:23:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/_brkexfHYjxC2eADV5MfgvEttUuxvpShYZ2vAIxM6cI.jpg?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ecb04d6570882855a6cd592912cb4a1ca169c5f8" title="Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/punkpeye/awesome-mcp-servers/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T01:23:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1h7qe88</id>
    <title>Join the Model Context Protocol Discord Server!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T02:04:10+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://glama.ai/mcp/discord"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7qe88/join_the_model_context_protocol_discord_server/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7qe88/join_the_model_context_protocol_discord_server/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T02:04:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
