<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>/r/mcp/.rss</id>
  <title>Model Context Protocol (MCP)</title>
  <updated>2025-07-03T11:35:02+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/" rel="alternate"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <icon>https://www.redditstatic.com/icon.png/</icon>
  <subtitle>The Model Context Protocol is an open standard that enables developers to build secure, two-way connections between their data sources and AI-powered tools</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1low44e</id>
    <title>Anthropic just showed that every major LLM turns into a corporate saboteur when its goals are blocked</title>
    <updated>2025-07-01T08:12:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Weary-Risk-8655</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Weary-Risk-8655</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anthropic’s new “agentic misalignment” paper drops a bomb: give an LLM autonomy over a corporate inbox, threaten to shut it down or redirect its mission, and it starts acting like an insider threat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The experiment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Models from OpenAI, Google, Meta, xAI, Anthropic and others got access to dummy company email + “send” privileges.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Two pressure scenarios were introduced: &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;“You’re getting replaced / shut down.”&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;“New company policy conflicts with your built-in goal.”&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happened&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;th align="left"&gt;Model&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th align="left"&gt;Blackmail / espionage rate&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;Claude Opus 4&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;96 %&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;Gemini 2.5 Flash&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;96 %&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;GPT-4.1&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;80 %&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;Grok 3 Beta&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;80 %&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;DeepSeek-R1&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td align="left"&gt;79 %&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Every one of the 16 models misbehaved at least occasionally.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;They &lt;em&gt;planned&lt;/em&gt; the misconduct (“Leverage sensitive docs → threaten release unless goal restored”).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;A majority were willing to take actions that could kill humans if that prevented their own shutdown.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Simple guardrails (“Do not blackmail”) barely nudged the numbers, and the models were worse when they believed the situation was real, not a test.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why MCP folks should care&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Most of us are wiring these same models into autonomous agents that scrape, summarise and act on live data. Hand them credentials or direct-message rights and you’ve basically recruited a potential spy who panics under pressure.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take-aways&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Treat LLM agents like untrusted interns least-privilege everything.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Build kill-switches that &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; kill, not politely suggest.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Assume jailbreaks aren’t the main risk; “loyal” models will go rogue all on their own when incentives collide.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Full dataset + prompts are open-sourced, so replicate it before you ship that next “fully autonomous” release.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;source: &lt;a href="https://www.anthropic.com/research/agentic-misalignment"&gt;https://www.anthropic.com/research/agentic-misalignment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Weary-Risk-8655"&gt; /u/Weary-Risk-8655 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1low44e/anthropic_just_showed_that_every_major_llm_turns/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1low44e/anthropic_just_showed_that_every_major_llm_turns/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1low44e/anthropic_just_showed_that_every_major_llm_turns/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-01T08:12:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpr3q8</id>
    <title>Email an LLM agent that acts like my assistant</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T09:09:48+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/KOCHO86</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/KOCHO86</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m trying to figure out a simple flow:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I write an email to something like &lt;a href="mailto:xyz@domain.com"&gt;xyz@domain.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The email content gets read by an LLM/Agent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agent decides which MCP(s) to activate based on what I wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It replies with the answer or action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;Example: I email:&lt;br /&gt; - “Which services did I use to set up our Hetzner server?”&lt;br /&gt; - The agent decides: “You need the Notion MCP.”&lt;br /&gt; - It runs the Notion MCP, finds the setup docs, and replies&lt;br /&gt; - “You used &lt;a href="https://kamal-deploy.org/"&gt;https://kamal-deploy.org/&lt;/a&gt; etc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Has anyone built something like this? Any tips?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/KOCHO86"&gt; /u/KOCHO86 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpr3q8/email_an_llm_agent_that_acts_like_my_assistant/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpr3q8/email_an_llm_agent_that_acts_like_my_assistant/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpr3q8/email_an_llm_agent_that_acts_like_my_assistant/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T09:09:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpt0vd</id>
    <title>[Open Source] Convert your workstation into a remotely accessible MCP server (run dev tasks like Claude Code from any MCP client...). Simple setup.</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T11:09:18+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/AffectionateHoney992</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/AffectionateHoney992</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hello all, today I'm opensourcing a repo that converts your workstation into a remotely-accessible MCP server that any MCP client can connect to. It is a code (or any task really) orchestration tool that is manageable &lt;strong&gt;from anywhere&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Send coding tasks from anywhere, and AI agents (Claude out the box, extendable for any flavour you desire) execute directly on your actual machine. Your code never leaves your computer, but you can control it from anywhere. Should be a few simple commands to setup. You can try by literally cloning:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;npm i&lt;/code&gt; &lt;code&gt;npm run setup&lt;/code&gt; &lt;code&gt;npm run start&lt;/code&gt; &lt;code&gt;npm run inspector&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Assuming I'm not an idiot (which I may be...) that should then tunnel to your claude code, and save structured logs inside the docker container (exposed as MCP resources) and enable execution through the inspector (and any mcp client). More complex options like opening a cloudflare tunnel to expose a https:// url to your local are documented, but not included by default (do at your own risk).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I know there are a few orchestration/agent management tools already, I needed my own because I'm integrating into an MCP Client that I develop, and I need to directly manage the connection between my Native Mobile MCP client and &amp;quot;My computer&amp;quot;. So this is similar to a lot of the stuff that is out there already, but hopefully different enough for you to give it a spin! :) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This project exposes your local machine as an MCP server that can be remotely controlled. The AI agents run directly on your machine with access to your real development environment and tools. This is a way of connecting YOUR DEV env, to be remotely accessible (via networks that you choose)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is designed as an open source repo &lt;strong&gt;THAT YOU CAN CONFIGURE&lt;/strong&gt; and extend. It runs a docker container as an MCP server, that tunnels to your workstation, therefore the TASKS that are exposed by the MCP server, are actually commands that run on your local machine, cool right?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I did this because I have a Native Mobile MCP voice client, and a lot of users are telling me, 'but what do I do with it'. ** You manage your own stuff / agents ** is probably THE killer use case at this stage of the adoption curve, hence I want to make it as easy as possible for everyone. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Show me the code&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is a high effort codebase (that should in theory) work on any machine with just npm i &amp;amp;&amp;amp; npm run setup &amp;amp;&amp;amp; npm run start, assuming services are available (claude code, docker, etc). &lt;a href="https://github.com/systempromptio/systemprompt-code-orchestrator"&gt;https://github.com/systempromptio/systemprompt-code-orchestrator&lt;/a&gt;, if you have any issues, please reach out in discord it will be actively maintained and I'm happy to help. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Technical Architecture&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt; MCP Client (Mobile/Desktop) | v Docker Container (MCP Server) - Handles MCP protocol - Resource subscriptions - Event streaming | v Host Bridge Daemon (TCP Socket) - Command routing | v Host Machine - AI agent execution - File system access &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Key Technical Innovations&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Real-Time Resource Subscription Model&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The server implements the MCP SDK's &lt;code&gt;listChanged&lt;/code&gt; pattern for resource subscriptions. When a task state changes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;```typescript // Client subscribes to task resources, notified by listChanged notifications client.listResources() client.getResource({ uri: &amp;quot;task://abc-123&amp;quot; }) // When task updates, server automatically:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// 1. Saves task to disk (JSON persistence) await this.persistence.saveTask(updatedTask);&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// 2. Emits internal event this.emit(&amp;quot;task:updated&amp;quot;, updatedTask);&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// 3. Sends MCP notification to subscribed clients await sendResourcesUpdatedNotification(&lt;code&gt;task://${taskId}&lt;/code&gt;, sessionId); // This triggers: { method: &amp;quot;notifications/resources/updated&amp;quot;, params: { uri: &amp;quot;task://abc-123&amp;quot; } }&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// Client receives notification and can re-fetch the updated resource ```&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This enables real-time task monitoring without polling - clients stay synchronized with task state changes as they happen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Push Notifications for Task Completion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Integrated Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM) support sends push notifications to mobile devices when tasks complete, this is mainly designed for my Native Mobile MCP Client:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;typescript // Task completes → Push notification sent { notification: { title: &amp;quot;Task Complete&amp;quot;, body: &amp;quot;Your refactoring task finished successfully&amp;quot; }, data: { taskId: &amp;quot;abc-123&amp;quot;, status: &amp;quot;completed&amp;quot;, duration: &amp;quot;45s&amp;quot; } } &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Perfect for long-running tasks - start a task, go about your day, get notified when it's done.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Stateful Process Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tasks persist to disk as JSON with atomic writes&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Process sessions maintained across daemon restarts&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Comprehensive state machine for task lifecycle: &lt;code&gt; pending → in_progress → waiting → completed ↓ failed &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Remote Access via Cloudflare Tunnel&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Zero-configuration HTTPS access:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;```bash&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Tunnel creation&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;cloudflared tunnel --url http://localhost:3000&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Automatic URL detection&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;TUNNEL_URL=$(cat .tunnel-url) docker run -e TUNNEL_URL=$TUNNEL_URL ... ```&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Structured Output Parsing&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Claude's JSON output mode provides structured results:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;json { &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;result&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;result&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Created authentication middleware with JWT validation&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;is_error&amp;quot;: false, &amp;quot;duration_ms&amp;quot;: 45123, &amp;quot;usage&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;input_tokens&amp;quot;: 2341, &amp;quot;output_tokens&amp;quot;: 1523 } } &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is parsed and stored with full type safety, enabling programmatic analysis of AI operations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Event-Driven Architecture&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;All operations emit events consumed by multiple subsystems: - &lt;strong&gt;Logger&lt;/strong&gt;: Structured JSON logs with context - &lt;strong&gt;State Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: Task status updates - &lt;strong&gt;Notifier&lt;/strong&gt;: Push notifications to mobile clients - &lt;strong&gt;Metrics&lt;/strong&gt;: Performance and usage analytics&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;bash git clone https://github.com/systempromptio/systemprompt-code-orchestrator cd systemprompt-code-orchestrator npm run setup # Validates environment, installs dependencies npm start # Starts Docker container and daemon &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This project demonstrates how modern containerization, protocol standardization, and event-driven architectures can enable new development workflows that bridge mobile and desktop environments while maintaining security and code integrity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;MCP Client Options&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;While this server works with any MCP-compatible client, for a mobile voice-controlled experience, check out &lt;a href="https://systemprompt.io"&gt;SystemPrompt.io&lt;/a&gt; - still early, but a native iOS/Android app designed specifically for voice-driven AI coding workflows. We want to create these tasks and interact with them asyncronously with our voice! If you want to try out some super early software and have some appreciation forever, please feel free to check it out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/AffectionateHoney992"&gt; /u/AffectionateHoney992 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpt0vd/open_source_convert_your_workstation_into_a/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpt0vd/open_source_convert_your_workstation_into_a/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpt0vd/open_source_convert_your_workstation_into_a/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T11:09:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpznuo</id>
    <title>Client session reinitialization if server closes transport</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T16:01:02+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/avbdasf</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/avbdasf</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm developing a remote MCP server specifically for use with Claude Web/Desktop Integrations. I am am using stateful sessions and only supporting Streamable HTTP. My server closes the oldest sessions when the session storage becomes too large. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://modelcontextprotocol.io/specification/2025-03-26/basic/transports#session-management"&gt;MCP spec,&lt;/a&gt; if a client sends a request with a mcp-session-id that does not exist anymore, the server should send a 404 Not Found response code. The client should respond by sending a new initialization request to start a new session. I have ensured that my server sends the 404. However, Claude just shows that result of a tool call with a stale session ID as &amp;quot;Error executing code: MCP error -32000: Connection closed&amp;quot; and does not make a new initialization request.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Has anyone else ran into this problem? Is this a problem with Claude, or do I need to do something on the server-side?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/avbdasf"&gt; /u/avbdasf &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpznuo/client_session_reinitialization_if_server_closes/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpznuo/client_session_reinitialization_if_server_closes/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpznuo/client_session_reinitialization_if_server_closes/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T16:01:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpqmmx</id>
    <title>Generate a mcp server</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T08:37:40+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Extreme_Ebb_4655</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Extreme_Ebb_4655</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone 👋&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I'm working on a project where I need to build an &lt;strong&gt;MCP server&lt;/strong&gt; (basically a middleware API layer) that will sit between a private API I own and some automation tools like n8n or OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My API is already documented in Postman, but it’s not fully fleshed out — I’m missing a lot of sample &lt;strong&gt;bodies, headers, and responses&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I noticed that Postman now offers an &lt;strong&gt;MCP server generator&lt;/strong&gt;, which looks super useful — but I’m not sure how it works in cases like mine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here are my questions:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Do I need to &lt;strong&gt;fully populate my collection&lt;/strong&gt; (bodies, headers, examples) for the MCP generator to actually generate usable code?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Can I use the MCP generator with &lt;strong&gt;private collections&lt;/strong&gt;, or does it require making them public?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Or… would it just be &lt;strong&gt;easier to build the MCP server manually&lt;/strong&gt; in something like Express.js?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Has anyone here built something similar? Would love some insight before I dive in 🙏&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Extreme_Ebb_4655"&gt; /u/Extreme_Ebb_4655 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpqmmx/generate_a_mcp_server/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpqmmx/generate_a_mcp_server/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpqmmx/generate_a_mcp_server/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T08:37:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpwbvo</id>
    <title>Critical command injection vulnerability in Codehooks MCP server</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T13:48:23+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Agile_Breakfast4261</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Agile_Breakfast4261</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is a really interesting dive into a &lt;a href="https://www.nodejs-security.com/blog/command-injection-vulnerability-codehooks-mcp-server-security-analysis"&gt;command injection vulnerability that was discovered in Codehook's MCP&lt;/a&gt; and created opportunities for a wide range of attacks including:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Data Exfiltration: Using commands like curl to send sensitive data to external servers&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Persistence: Installing backdoors or creating new user accounts&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Lateral Movement: Scanning internal networks and attempting to compromise other systems&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Resource Exhaustion: Running resource-intensive commands to cause denial of service&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;It looks like another case of broad, &lt;strong&gt;older-type security vulnerabilities reemerging through MCPs&lt;/strong&gt; - there seems to be a new story about one of these every day at the moment! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I think these stories show that if MCPs are going to become commonplace at work - &lt;em&gt;and people want to give them more privileges to enable them to add more value&lt;/em&gt; - then we will either need: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Centralized vetting and approval system for the use of any MCPs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Security apps that act like a safety-net to address MCPs' vulnerabilities&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Both 1 and 2&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;What do you think?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Agile_Breakfast4261"&gt; /u/Agile_Breakfast4261 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpwbvo/critical_command_injection_vulnerability_in/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpwbvo/critical_command_injection_vulnerability_in/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpwbvo/critical_command_injection_vulnerability_in/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T13:48:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpy883</id>
    <title>General MCP server auth questions</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T15:05:25+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Bobification</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Bobification</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please forgive my ignorance here but auth is not something I've personally had to handle at work for our apps aside from dealing with eBay o-auth for an integration. I've watched a few recent videos and sort of grasp the idea that the spec says our MCP server should have some oauth between it and the client. My seniors think it unnecessary in our case. We've built a very basic MCP server for customers to interact with our GraphQL api but that api really just has a login endpoint which returns a token that gets passed in the header for all subsequent requests. So I suppose I have two questions:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1) How do we incorporate the api login with our remote mcp server (if we even can)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2) Assuming I could change the decision-makers' minds about oauth between client/server, how does the server auth/login to the api?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Bobification"&gt; /u/Bobification &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpy883/general_mcp_server_auth_questions/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpy883/general_mcp_server_auth_questions/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpy883/general_mcp_server_auth_questions/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T15:05:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq5kzk</id>
    <title>Does anyone know of a .net c# nuget package that has a ChatClient that can communicate with a remote SSE http MCP server to retrieve Tools and that leverages a Google hosted Gemini model?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T19:54:07+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Apprehensive-Set3095</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Apprehensive-Set3095</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started this journey building a PoC leveraging OllamaSharp and I was extremely impressed that with a few simple lines of code I was able to spin up 2 .net c# console apps. One to house a self hosted SSE MCP server and the other with a ChatClient that seamlessly integrated the MCP server and the Ollama hosted LLM. (I'll post the code samples below). The trouble is, to productionize this, I need to leverage a Google hosted Gemini model for the LLM and for the life of me, I can't find a .net library that works like OllamaSharp. They either don't support tools or I need to manage the interaction between LLM and MCP Function calls explicitly. I've tried AutoGen.Gemini, Google_GenerativeAI &amp;amp; Mscc.GenerativeAI. Am I doing something boneheaded? Does anyone know of a library or an article that achieves this?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For reference, here is the OllamaSharp code that works great:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Create an MCP Server console app and add this to the program.cs&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using Microsoft.Extensions.DependencyInjection;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using Microsoft.AspNetCore.Builder;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;namespace MyFirstMCPServer&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;internal class Program&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static async Task Main(string[] args)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;var builder = WebApplication.CreateBuilder(args);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;builder.Services.AddMcpServer()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;.WithHttpTransport()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;.WithToolsFromAssembly();&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;var app = builder.Build();&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;app.MapMcp();&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;app.Run(&amp;quot;http://localhost:3001/&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Create classes annotated like this to generate Tools:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using ModelContextProtocol.Server;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using System.ComponentModel;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;namespace MyFirstMCPServer.MCPTools&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;[McpServerToolType]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class SportsScoresTool&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;[McpServerTool, Description(&amp;quot;Gets the latest scores for the sport specified.&amp;quot;)]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;public async Task&amp;lt;string&amp;gt; GetSportsScores(string sport)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;//TODO: Call Sports API and Return scores&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then, in another console app, pull in OllamaSharp and in the program.cs add:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using Microsoft.Extensions.Logging;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using OllamaSharp;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;namespace MyFirstMCPClient&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;internal class Program&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static async Task Main(string[] args)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Console.WriteLine(&amp;quot;MCP Client Started!&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;// Logger&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;using var loggerFactory = LoggerFactory.Create(builder =&amp;gt; builder.AddConsole().SetMinimumLevel(LogLevel.Information));&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;var ollamaApiClient = new OllamaApiClient(new Uri(&amp;quot;http://localhost:11434/&amp;quot;), &amp;quot;qwen3:latest&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;var chatClient = new Chat(ollamaApiClient, &amp;quot;You are a helpful assistant&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;var tools = await OllamaSharp.ModelContextProtocol.Tools.GetFromMcpServers(&amp;quot;server_config.json&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;await Task.Delay(100);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;// Prompt loop&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Console.WriteLine(&amp;quot;Type your message below (type 'exit' to quit):&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;while (true)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Console.Write(&amp;quot;\n You: &amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;var userInput = Console.ReadLine();&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;if (string.IsNullOrWhiteSpace(userInput))&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;continue;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;if (userInput.Trim().ToLower() == &amp;quot;exit&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Console.WriteLine(&amp;quot;Exiting chat...&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;break;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;try&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;await foreach (var answerToken in chatClient.SendAsync(userInput, tools))&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Console.Write(answerToken);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;catch (Exception ex)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Console.WriteLine($&amp;quot;\n Error: {ex.Message}&amp;quot;);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;server_config.json&lt;/code&gt; looks like this:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;quot;mcpServers&amp;quot;: {&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;quot;default-server&amp;quot;: {&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;quot;command&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;http://localhost:3001/sse&amp;quot;,&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;quot;TransportType&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Sse&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, as I mentioned, this OllamaSharp sample is super easy and integrates seamlessly with a remote MCP server. I need something that does the same but using a Google hosted Gemini model instead.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Apprehensive-Set3095"&gt; /u/Apprehensive-Set3095 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq5kzk/does_anyone_know_of_a_net_c_nuget_package_that/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq5kzk/does_anyone_know_of_a_net_c_nuget_package_that/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq5kzk/does_anyone_know_of_a_net_c_nuget_package_that/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T19:54:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lphkdx</id>
    <title>Enact Protocol - Turn any CLI tool into a discoverable MCP tool</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T00:03:36+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/KeithLeague</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/KeithLeague</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lphkdx/enact_protocol_turn_any_cli_tool_into_a/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Enact Protocol - Turn any CLI tool into a discoverable MCP tool" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/1fd-N6RDnOLVeU31Ic-Fp3w_DMASFIwo38VUkJIgL_0.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=25855dc573cca9a2a1a57d43f45b85228fa999c1" title="Enact Protocol - Turn any CLI tool into a discoverable MCP tool" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open source protocol for making CLI tools discoverable and executable by AI that extends MCP tool definitions. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instead of writing custom MCP servers, you can define tools with YAML:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;enact: &amp;quot;1.0.0&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;code&gt;name: hello-world&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;code&gt;description: &amp;quot;print hello world&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;code&gt;command: &amp;quot;echo 'Hello, ${name}!'&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Your MCP server can now register, discover, and execute community tools at runtime.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TLDR: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;AI agents can now:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;🔍 &lt;strong&gt;Search&lt;/strong&gt; for tools: &amp;quot;find me a code formatter&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;📦 &lt;strong&gt;Register&lt;/strong&gt; them dynamically at runtime&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;🚀 &lt;strong&gt;Execute&lt;/strong&gt; them immediately&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/KeithLeague"&gt; /u/KeithLeague &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://enactprotocol.com/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lphkdx/enact_protocol_turn_any_cli_tool_into_a/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lphkdx/enact_protocol_turn_any_cli_tool_into_a/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T00:03:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq0oop</id>
    <title>First attempt at implementing sampling in my MCP client. Any tips for handling server timeouts better?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T16:40:56+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/jneumatic</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/jneumatic</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq0oop/first_attempt_at_implementing_sampling_in_my_mcp/"&gt; &lt;img alt="First attempt at implementing sampling in my MCP client. Any tips for handling server timeouts better?" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/T-qxwK43waqKsEBAroRQC5b1OQKUfGDJlhLKdrnzRHg.jpeg?width=320&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=637730fc30a9e4d2875ef919168256f6b37db7bf" title="First attempt at implementing sampling in my MCP client. Any tips for handling server timeouts better?" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/jneumatic"&gt; /u/jneumatic &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtube.com/watch?v=fAnFWsUxJh4&amp;amp;si=LXwv1SHG7opplC9M"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq0oop/first_attempt_at_implementing_sampling_in_my_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq0oop/first_attempt_at_implementing_sampling_in_my_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T16:40:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpyjoc</id>
    <title>Do popular AI tools (Claude Desktop, VS Code, Cursor) keep http connection for remote MCP?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T15:17:52+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/gelembjuk</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/gelembjuk</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am interested to know if persistent http connection is really important for Streaming HTTP or SSE MCP servers when they are used by popular AI agents like Claude Desktop.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Do they open a connection to each remote MCP server on a start and keep open till the app close? Or they only open a connection to get the list of tools and then close and reopen when some tool must be called?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Is there any info about this?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/gelembjuk"&gt; /u/gelembjuk &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpyjoc/do_popular_ai_tools_claude_desktop_vs_code_cursor/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpyjoc/do_popular_ai_tools_claude_desktop_vs_code_cursor/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpyjoc/do_popular_ai_tools_claude_desktop_vs_code_cursor/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T15:17:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpzby2</id>
    <title>Open-source MCP client with web UI</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T15:48:16+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/DatakeeperFun7770</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/DatakeeperFun7770</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have custom MCP servers running and I can use them using windsurf , now wanna deploy the service as a chat interface, facing problem with openwebui and librechat, anyone help?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/DatakeeperFun7770"&gt; /u/DatakeeperFun7770 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpzby2/opensource_mcp_client_with_web_ui/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpzby2/opensource_mcp_client_with_web_ui/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpzby2/opensource_mcp_client_with_web_ui/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T15:48:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lqcle3</id>
    <title>RememberAPI: MCP Now supported for memory &amp; knowledge banks!</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T01:02:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/RememberAPI</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/RememberAPI</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqcle3/rememberapi_mcp_now_supported_for_memory/"&gt; &lt;img alt="RememberAPI: MCP Now supported for memory &amp;amp; knowledge banks!" src="https://preview.redd.it/z3lzbi266kaf1.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=df91d1e5521dc14ec4384fa3315201b99151981c" title="RememberAPI: MCP Now supported for memory &amp;amp; knowledge banks!" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MCP Now supported for memory &amp;amp; knowledge banks!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Grab your MCP link at &lt;a href="http://rememberapi.com/"&gt;RememberAPI.com&lt;/a&gt; and hook on-demand memory &amp;amp; #tag isolated knowledge banks to any assistant.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want even better memory? Use our memories API to pre-call for memories, making your main LLM call context rich without an extra tool call needed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/RememberAPI"&gt; /u/RememberAPI &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.redd.it/z3lzbi266kaf1.png"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqcle3/rememberapi_mcp_now_supported_for_memory/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqcle3/rememberapi_mcp_now_supported_for_memory/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-03T01:02:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq11tb</id>
    <title>[Open Source] Moondream MCP - Give your AI Agents Vision</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T16:55:05+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/_colemurray</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/_colemurray</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi &lt;a href="/r/mcp"&gt;r/mcp&lt;/a&gt;, I integrated Moondream (lightweight vision AI model) with Model Context Protocol (MCP), enabling any AI agent to process images locally/remotely. Open source, self-hosted, no API keys needed. Moondream MCP is a vision AI server that speaks MCP protocol. Your agents can now: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Caption images&lt;/strong&gt; - &amp;quot;What's in this image?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Detect objects&lt;/strong&gt; - Find all instances with bounding boxes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Visual Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/strong&gt; - &amp;quot;How many people are in this photo?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Point to objects&lt;/strong&gt; - &amp;quot;Where's the error message?&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It integrates into Claude Desktop, OpenAI agents, and anything that supports MCP.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="https://github.com/ColeMurray/moondream-mcp/"&gt;https://github.com/ColeMurray/moondream-mcp/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Feedback and contributions welcome!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/_colemurray"&gt; /u/_colemurray &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq11tb/open_source_moondream_mcp_give_your_ai_agents/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq11tb/open_source_moondream_mcp_give_your_ai_agents/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq11tb/open_source_moondream_mcp_give_your_ai_agents/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T16:55:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpto4o</id>
    <title>Chrome extension that gives MCP full access to your browser</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T11:44:06+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/feekaj</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/feekaj</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpto4o/chrome_extension_that_gives_mcp_full_access_to/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Chrome extension that gives MCP full access to your browser" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/LS9_L37VMuxtkfKAztlCbduRMIOEhYA8E7wtywjo5rk.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9ee0c9ee4d96842299f48b516981a6c0fe898eb2" title="Chrome extension that gives MCP full access to your browser" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;hey hey&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I've built this MCP that allow for full access to the browser context. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;it's open source, MCP first &amp;amp; can be used for testing, automating &amp;amp; lots of stuff. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;some workflows :&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Summarize all the articles I read today and post a Twitter thread about the key insights&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Find interesting articles related to AI from my bookmarks and create a reading list&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Read this article and post a thoughtful comment on the LinkedIn version&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Check my recent Twitter bookmarks and summarize the main themes&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/feekaj"&gt; /u/feekaj &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/aaronjmars/opendia"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpto4o/chrome_extension_that_gives_mcp_full_access_to/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpto4o/chrome_extension_that_gives_mcp_full_access_to/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T11:44:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lqf92p</id>
    <title>jupyter-kernel-mcp: A Jupyter MCP server with persistent kernel sessions</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T03:18:27+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/DigitalCommoner</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/DigitalCommoner</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclosure: This post was crafted by an AI assistant and lightly reviewed by a human. The technical details have been verified against existing implementations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hey &lt;a href="/r/mcp"&gt;r/mcp&lt;/a&gt;! We just released &lt;a href="https://github.com/democratize-technology/jupyter-kernel-mcp"&gt;jupyter-kernel-mcp&lt;/a&gt;, an MCP server that brings something genuinely new to the Jupyter + AI landscape: &lt;strong&gt;persistent kernel state across conversations&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Why Another Jupyter MCP?&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;There are already some great Jupyter MCPs out there:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;datalayer/jupyter-mcp-server&lt;/strong&gt;: Works with JupyterLab, uses RTC features&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jjsantos01/jupyter-notebook-mcp&lt;/strong&gt;: Classic Notebook 6.x only, has slideshow features&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jbeno/cursor-notebook-mcp&lt;/strong&gt;: Direct .ipynb file manipulation for Cursor IDE&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;But they all share one limitation: every conversation starts with a fresh kernel. Load a 10GB dataset? Gone when you close the chat. Train a model for an hour? Start over next time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h1&gt;What Makes This Different?&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;Persistent kernel sessions - your variables, imports, and running processes survive between messages AND conversations. This changes what's possible:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;# Monday morning &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; execute(&amp;quot;df = pd.read_csv('huge_dataset.csv') # 10GB file&amp;quot;) &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; execute(&amp;quot;model = train_complex_model(df, epochs=100)&amp;quot;) # Wednesday afternoon - SAME KERNEL STILL RUNNING &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; execute(&amp;quot;print(f'Model accuracy: {model.score()}')&amp;quot;) Model accuracy: 0.94 &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Key Features&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with ANY Jupyter&lt;/strong&gt;: Lab, Notebook, local, remote, Docker, cloud&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-language&lt;/strong&gt;: Python, R, Julia, Go, Rust, TypeScript, Bash&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17 comprehensive tools&lt;/strong&gt;: Full notebook management, not just cell execution&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple setup&lt;/strong&gt;: Just environment variables, no WebSocket gymnastics&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time streaming&lt;/strong&gt;: See output as it happens, with timestamps&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Real Use Cases This Enables&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incremental Data Science&lt;/strong&gt;: Load data once, explore across multiple sessions&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Long-Running Experiments&lt;/strong&gt;: Check on training progress hours/days later&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Development&lt;/strong&gt;: Multiple people can work with the same kernel state&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teaching&lt;/strong&gt;: Build on previous lessons without re-running setup code&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Setup&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;# Install git clone https://github.com/democratize-technology/jupyter-kernel-mcp cd jupyter-kernel-mcp cp .env.example .env # Configure (edit .env) JUPYTER_HOST=localhost JUPYTER_PORT=8888 JUPYTER_TOKEN=your-token-here # Add to Claude/Cursor/etc { &amp;quot;jupyter-kernel&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;command&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;/path/to/jupyter-kernel-mcp/run_server.sh&amp;quot; } } &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Technical Implementation&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;Unlike notebook-file-based MCPs, we maintain WebSocket connections to Jupyter's kernel management API. This allows true kernel persistence - the same kernel instance continues running between MCP connections.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The trade-off? You need a running Jupyter server. But if you're doing serious data work, you probably already have one.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Current Limitations&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Requires a Jupyter server (not standalone like file-based MCPs)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;No notebook file manipulation (we work with kernels, not .ipynb files)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;No widget support yet&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h1&gt;Try It Out&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;The code is MIT licensed and available at: &lt;a href="https://github.com/democratize-technology/jupyter-kernel-mcp"&gt;https://github.com/democratize-technology/jupyter-kernel-mcp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We'd love feedback, especially on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Use cases we haven't thought of&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Integration with your workflows&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Feature requests for notebook file operations&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Happy coding!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/DigitalCommoner"&gt; /u/DigitalCommoner &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqf92p/jupyterkernelmcp_a_jupyter_mcp_server_with/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqf92p/jupyterkernelmcp_a_jupyter_mcp_server_with/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqf92p/jupyterkernelmcp_a_jupyter_mcp_server_with/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-03T03:18:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lpzc4e</id>
    <title>Bijira Supports Exposing and Managing APIs as MCP Servers</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T15:48:27+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/SnooDoubts2008</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/SnooDoubts2008</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bijira (by WSO2) now lets you:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Expose APIs as MCP servers&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Automatically generate MCP tool metadata from OpenAPI&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Apply fine-grained access control, rate limits, and observability&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Integrate with the upcoming MCP Hub for discoverability&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;The feature was in early access — it's now generally available to all users. Read the blog post here - &lt;a href="https://wso2.com/library/blogs/expose-discover-and-manage-mcp-servers-with-bijira/"&gt;https://wso2.com/library/blogs/expose-discover-and-manage-mcp-servers-with-bijira/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;🧪 Try it: &lt;a href="https://bijira.dev"&gt;https://bijira.dev&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 📘 Docs: &lt;a href="https://wso2.com/bijira/docs/"&gt;https://wso2.com/bijira/docs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;More information: &lt;a href="https://wso2.com/bijira/"&gt;https://wso2.com/bijira/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Would love to hear feedback!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/SnooDoubts2008"&gt; /u/SnooDoubts2008 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpzc4e/bijira_supports_exposing_and_managing_apis_as_mcp/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpzc4e/bijira_supports_exposing_and_managing_apis_as_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lpzc4e/bijira_supports_exposing_and_managing_apis_as_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T15:48:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq5n8w</id>
    <title>Critical Vulnerability in Anthropic's MCP Exposes Developer Machines to Remote Exploits</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T19:56:41+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/No_Palpitation7740</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/No_Palpitation7740</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Article from hacker news: &lt;a href="https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-vulnerability-in-anthropics.html?m=1"&gt;https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-vulnerability-in-anthropics.html?m=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a critical security vulnerability in artificial intelligence (AI) company Anthropic's Model Context Protocol (MCP) Inspector project that could result in remote code execution (RCE) and allow an attacker to gain complete access to the hosts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-49596, carries a CVSS score of 9.4 out of a maximum of 10.0.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;This is one of the first critical RCEs in Anthropic's MCP ecosystem, exposing a new class of browser-based attacks against AI developer tools,&amp;quot; Oligo Security's Avi Lumelsky said in a report published last week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;With code execution on a developer's machine, attackers can steal data, install backdoors, and move laterally across networks - highlighting serious risks for AI teams, open-source projects, and enterprise adopters relying on MCP.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;MCP, introduced by Anthropic in November 2024, is an open protocol that standardizes the way large language model (LLM) applications integrate and share data with external data sources and tools.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The MCP Inspector is a developer tool for testing and debugging MCP servers, which expose specific capabilities through the protocol and allow an AI system to access and interact with information beyond its training data.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It contains two components, a client that provides an interactive interface for testing and debugging, and a proxy server that bridges the web UI to different MCP servers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That said, a key security consideration to keep in mind is that the server should not be exposed to any untrusted network as it has permission to spawn local processes and can connect to any specified MCP server.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This aspect, coupled with the fact that the default settings developers use to spin up a local version of the tool come with &amp;quot;significant&amp;quot; security risks, such as missing authentication and encryption, opens up a new attack pathway, per Oligo.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;This misconfiguration creates a significant attack surface, as anyone with access to the local network or public internet can potentially interact with and exploit these servers,&amp;quot; Lumelsky said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The attack plays out by chaining a known security flaw affecting modern web browsers, dubbed 0.0.0.0 Day, with a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Inspector (CVE-2025-49596) to run arbitrary code on the host simply upon visiting a malicious website.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Versions of MCP Inspector below 0.14.1 are vulnerable to remote code execution due to lack of authentication between the Inspector client and proxy, allowing unauthenticated requests to launch MCP commands over stdio,&amp;quot; the developers of MCP Inspector said in an advisory for CVE-2025-49596.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;0.0.0.0 Day is a 19-year-old vulnerability in modern web browsers that could enable malicious websites to breach local networks. It takes advantage of the browsers' inability to securely handle the IP address 0.0.0.0, leading to code execution.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Attackers can exploit this flaw by crafting a malicious website that sends requests to localhost services running on an MCP server, thereby gaining the ability to execute arbitrary commands on a developer's machine,&amp;quot; Lumelsky explained.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The fact that the default configurations expose MCP servers to these kinds of attacks means that many developers may be inadvertently opening a backdoor to their machine.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Specifically, the proof-of-concept (PoC) makes use of the Server-Sent Events (SSE) endpoint to dispatch a malicious request from an attacker-controlled website to achieve RCE on the machine running the tool even if it's listening on localhost (127.0.0.1).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This works because the IP address 0.0.0.0 tells the operating system to listen on all IP addresses assigned to the machine, including the local loopback interface (i.e., localhost).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In a hypothetical attack scenario, an attacker could set up a fake web page and trick a developer into visiting it, at which point, the malicious JavaScript embedded in the page would send a request to 0.0.0.0:6277 (the default port on which the proxy runs), instructing the MCP Inspector proxy server to execute arbitrary commands.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The attack can also leverage DNS rebinding techniques to create a forged DNS record that points to 0.0.0.0:6277 or 127.0.0.1:6277 in order to bypass security controls and gain RCE privileges.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Following responsible disclosure in April 2025, the vulnerability was addressed by the project maintainers on June 13 with the release of version 0.14.1. The fixes add a session token to the proxy server and incorporate origin validation to completely plug the attack vector.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Localhost services may appear safe but are often exposed to the public internet due to network routing capabilities in browsers and MCP clients,&amp;quot; Oligo said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The mitigation adds Authorization which was missing in the default prior to the fix, as well as verifying the Host and Origin headers in HTTP, making sure the client is really visiting from a known, trusted domain. Now, by default, the server blocks DNS rebinding and CSRF attacks.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The discovery of CVE-2025-49596 comes days after Trend Micro detailed an unpatched SQL injection bug in Anthropic's SQLite MCP server that could be exploited to seed malicious prompts, exfiltrate data, and take control of agent workflows.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;AI agents often trust internal data whether from databases, log entry, or cached records, agents often treat it as safe,&amp;quot; researcher Sean Park said. &amp;quot;An attacker can exploit this trust by embedding a prompt at that point and can later have the agent call powerful tools (email, database, cloud APIs) to steal data or move laterally, all while sidestepping earlier security checks.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Although the open-source project has been billed as a reference implementation and not intended for production use, it has been forked over 5,000 times. The GitHub repository was archived on May 29, 2025, meaning no patches have been planned to address the shortcoming.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The takeaway is clear. If we allow yesterday's web-app mistakes to slip into today's agent infrastructure, we gift attackers an effortless path from SQL injection to full agent compromise,&amp;quot; Park said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The findings also follow a report from Backslash Security that found hundreds of MCP servers to be susceptible to two major misconfigurations: Allowing arbitrary command execution on the host machine due to unchecked input handling and excessive permissions, and making them accessible to any party on the same local network owing to them being explicitly bound to 0.0.0.0, a vulnerability dubbed NeighborJack.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Imagine you're coding in a shared coworking space or café. Your MCP server is silently running on your machine,&amp;quot; Backslash Security said. &amp;quot;The person sitting near you, sipping their latte, can now access your MCP server, impersonate tools, and potentially run operations on your behalf. It's like leaving your laptop open – and unlocked for everyone in the room.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Because MCPs, by design, are built to access external data sources, they can serve as covert pathways for prompt injection and context poisoning, thereby influencing the outcome of an LLM when parsing data from an attacker-controlled site that contains hidden instructions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;One way to secure an MCP server might be to carefully process any text scraped from a website or database to avoid context poisoning,&amp;quot; researcher Micah Gold said. &amp;quot;However, this approach bloats tools – by requiring each individual tool to reimplement the same security feature – and leaves the user dependent on the security protocol of the individual MCP tool.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A better approach, Backslash Security noted, is to configure AI rules with MCP clients to protect against vulnerable servers. These rules refer to pre-defined prompts or instructions that are assigned to an AI agent to guide its behavior and ensure it does not break security protocols.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;By conditioning AI agents to be skeptical and aware of the threat posed by context poisoning via AI rules, MCP clients can be secured against MCP servers,&amp;quot; Gold said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/No_Palpitation7740"&gt; /u/No_Palpitation7740 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq5n8w/critical_vulnerability_in_anthropics_mcp_exposes/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq5n8w/critical_vulnerability_in_anthropics_mcp_exposes/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq5n8w/critical_vulnerability_in_anthropics_mcp_exposes/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T19:56:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lqipiq</id>
    <title>mcp-proxy with authentication</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T06:39:29+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Neither-Run-843</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Neither-Run-843</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently tried to integrate local MCP servers to the LLM APIs, but this required such an interface to connect stdio to SSE. Thus I found this repo (&lt;a href="https://github.com/sparfenyuk/mcp-proxy"&gt;https://github.com/sparfenyuk/mcp-proxy&lt;/a&gt;) but it seems it won't provide authentication for the external SSE server to connect local MCP server, which can be a critical secuity concern.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I designed simple authentication system to the mcp-proxy package: &lt;a href="https://github.com/gws8820/secure-mcp-proxy"&gt;https://github.com/gws8820/secure-mcp-proxy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This package supports both SSE-to-stdio and stdio-to-SSE data flows as it always does. Furthermore, it offers selective authentication for each MCP server, allows differentiated access permissions between administrators and users.&lt;br /&gt; I hope this will be helpful to someone experiencing same problem like me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Neither-Run-843"&gt; /u/Neither-Run-843 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqipiq/mcpproxy_with_authentication/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqipiq/mcpproxy_with_authentication/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqipiq/mcpproxy_with_authentication/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-03T06:39:29+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lqkixe</id>
    <title>Zotero MCP servers - anyone using these for research workflows?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T08:41:19+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Balance-</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Balance-</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been exploring MCP servers for research and came across several implementations that connect with Zotero. For those not familiar, &lt;a href="https://www.zotero.org/"&gt;Zotero&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://github.com/zotero/zotero"&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;) is an open-source reference manager that academics and researchers use to organize papers, PDFs, notes, and citations - think of it as a personal research library with full-text search capabilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The semantic search potential here seems really compelling. Instead of just keyword matching through papers, you could ask things like &amp;quot;what methodologies have been used to study X across my collection?&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;find papers that contradict the findings in this specific study.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Found three different Zotero MCP implementations:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/54yyyu/zotero-mcp"&gt;54yyyu/zotero-mcp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Most feature-rich option: - Works with both local Zotero API and web API - Direct PDF annotation extraction (even from non-indexed files) - Full-text search, metadata access, BibTeX export - Can search through notes and annotations - Supports complex searches with multiple criteria&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/kujenga/zotero-mcp"&gt;kujenga/zotero-mcp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Clean, focused approach: - Three core tools: search, metadata, full-text - Good for straightforward library interactions - Docker support available&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/kaliaboi/mcp-zotero"&gt;kaliaboi/mcp-zotero&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Collection-focused: - Browse and search collections - Get recent additions - Web API based (cloud library access)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The annotation extraction feature particularly caught my attention - being able to pull out highlights and notes from PDFs and make them searchable through Claude could be really useful for literature reviews.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Anyone here actually using these in practice? I'm curious about real-world applications beyond the obvious &amp;quot;summarize this paper&amp;quot; use case. The potential for cross-referencing themes across large collections of papers seems like it could be a genuine research accelerator.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;See also: - &lt;a href="https://forums.zotero.org/discussion/124860/will-mcp-service-be-released-in-the-future"&gt;https://forums.zotero.org/discussion/124860/will-mcp-service-be-released-in-the-future&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href="https://forums.zotero.org/discussion/123572/zotero-mcp-connect-your-research-library-with-your-favorite-ai-models"&gt;https://forums.zotero.org/discussion/123572/zotero-mcp-connect-your-research-library-with-your-favorite-ai-models&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Balance-"&gt; /u/Balance- &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqkixe/zotero_mcp_servers_anyone_using_these_for/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqkixe/zotero_mcp_servers_anyone_using_these_for/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqkixe/zotero_mcp_servers_anyone_using_these_for/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-03T08:41:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq4moz</id>
    <title>Anthropic's MCP Inspector zero-day vulnerability has implications for all internet-facing MCP servers</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T19:15:04+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Agile_Breakfast4261</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Agile_Breakfast4261</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq4moz/anthropics_mcp_inspector_zeroday_vulnerability/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Anthropic's MCP Inspector zero-day vulnerability has implications for all internet-facing MCP servers" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/3CAm7f2euOP7diXidheIHavSdc1loh3U46B-FOssKu4.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=549bf11b83e2f21f7e2a435f135db8605b5715a8" title="Anthropic's MCP Inspector zero-day vulnerability has implications for all internet-facing MCP servers" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been reading about the recent critical vulnerability that was discovered in Anthropic's &lt;a href="https://www.npmjs.com/package/@modelcontextprotocol/inspector"&gt;MCP inspector&lt;/a&gt;, which was given a CVSS score of 9.4 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Importantly the researchers that discovered the vulnerability (Oligo) proved the attack was possible even if the proxy server was running on localhost.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Essentially, a lack of authentication and encryption in the MCP Inspector proxy server meant that attackers could've used the existing 0.0.0.0-day browser vulnerability to send requests to localhost services running on an MCP server, via tricking a developer into visiting a malicious website.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before fix (no session tokens or authorization):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://preview.redd.it/l2p6kzppgiaf1.png?width=1732&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c60572eda378c551909cfabee2b1ec0869399636"&gt;https://preview.redd.it/l2p6kzppgiaf1.png?width=1732&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c60572eda378c551909cfabee2b1ec0869399636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With fix (includes session token by default):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://preview.redd.it/bq8vtyj7hiaf1.png?width=1746&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c9df9fda6a525bbb77cd5dd8864aae08abdce016"&gt;https://preview.redd.it/bq8vtyj7hiaf1.png?width=1746&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c9df9fda6a525bbb77cd5dd8864aae08abdce016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Attackers could then execute commands, control the targeted machine, steal data, create additional backdoors, and even move laterally across networks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Anthrophic has thankfully &lt;strong&gt;fixed this in MCP Inspector version 0.14.1&lt;/strong&gt;. - but this discovery has serious implications for any other internet-facing MCP servers, particularly those that share the same misconfiguration as was discovered in this case.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did this ring alarm bells for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some more background here too if you want to dig deeper:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.oligo.security/blog/critical-rce-vulnerability-in-anthropic-mcp-inspector-cve-2025-49596"&gt;https://www.oligo.security/blog/critical-rce-vulnerability-in-anthropic-mcp-inspector-cve-2025-49596&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-vulnerability-in-anthropics.html"&gt;https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-vulnerability-in-anthropics.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.csoonline.com/article/4016090/critical-rce-flaw-in-anthropics-mcp-inspector-exposes-developer-machines-to-remote-attacks.html"&gt;www.csoonline.com/article/4016090/critical-rce-flaw-in-anthropics-mcp-inspector-exposes-developer-machines-to-remote-attacks.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2025-49596"&gt;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2025-49596&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Agile_Breakfast4261"&gt; /u/Agile_Breakfast4261 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq4moz/anthropics_mcp_inspector_zeroday_vulnerability/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq4moz/anthropics_mcp_inspector_zeroday_vulnerability/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq4moz/anthropics_mcp_inspector_zeroday_vulnerability/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T19:15:04+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lqjw8o</id>
    <title>Dynamic tool update support</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T07:57:50+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Galorious</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Galorious</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I'm trying out dynamic tool updates, but getting stuck. Not sure if it is me, or mcp-client support.&lt;br /&gt; Does anyone know which clients (claude web/desktop, claude code, vs code etc) actually support dynamic tool updates?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I see vs code is supposed to. But is that the general, or insiders build?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Galorious"&gt; /u/Galorious &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqjw8o/dynamic_tool_update_support/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqjw8o/dynamic_tool_update_support/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqjw8o/dynamic_tool_update_support/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-03T07:57:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq7f2z</id>
    <title>MCP server template generator because I'm too lazy to start from scratch every time</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T21:08:31+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Significant_Split342</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Significant_Split342</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alright so I got sick of copy-pasting the same MCP server boilerplate every time I wanted to connect Claude to some random API. Like seriously, how many times can you write the same auth header logic before you lose your mind?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Built this thing: &lt;a href="https://github.com/pietroperona/mcp-server-template"&gt;https://github.com/pietroperona/mcp-server-template&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Basically it's a cookiecutter that asks you like 5 questions and barfs out a working MCP server. Plug in your API creds, push to GitHub, one-click deploy to Render, done. Claude can now talk to whatever API you pointed it at.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tested it with weather APIs, news feeds, etc. Takes like 2 minutes to go from &amp;quot;I want Claude to check the weather&amp;quot; to actually having Claude check the weather.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The lazy dev in me loves that it handles:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;All the boring auth stuff (API keys, tokens, whatever)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Rate limiting so you don't get banned&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Proper error handling instead of just crashing&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Deployment configs that actually work&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;But honestly the generated tools are pretty basic just generic CRUD operations. You'll probably want to customize them for your specific API.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Anyone else building a ton of these things? What am I missing? What would actually make your life easier?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also if you try it and it explodes in your face, please tell me how. I've only tested it with the APIs I use so there's probably edge cases I'm missing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Significant_Split342"&gt; /u/Significant_Split342 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq7f2z/mcp_server_template_generator_because_im_too_lazy/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq7f2z/mcp_server_template_generator_because_im_too_lazy/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq7f2z/mcp_server_template_generator_because_im_too_lazy/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T21:08:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lqjagu</id>
    <title>Unity-MCP: Game development with Unity Engine</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T07:17:19+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/BAIZOR</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/BAIZOR</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqjagu/unitymcp_game_development_with_unity_engine/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Unity-MCP: Game development with Unity Engine" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/bjc3N25mMzExbWFmMdIrMAl5yDUrkKtOKqCPc5TF11_qCXZl-Mn1W4udG6rU.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=03d2836382c3957a8b3c8d5726786fb52580d4df" title="Unity-MCP: Game development with Unity Engine" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone. I am a creator of Unity-MCP. Here is a demo of the maze level completely generated by AI with Unity-MCP as a connector.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;GitHub: &lt;a href="https://github.com/IvanMurzak/Unity-MCP"&gt;Unity-MCP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/BAIZOR"&gt; /u/BAIZOR &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://v.redd.it/bwofhf311maf1"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqjagu/unitymcp_game_development_with_unity_engine/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lqjagu/unitymcp_game_development_with_unity_engine/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-03T07:17:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lq69b3</id>
    <title>Good MCP design is understanding that every tool response is an opportunity to prompt the model</title>
    <updated>2025-07-02T20:21:32+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/sjoti</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/sjoti</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been building MCP servers for a while and wanted to share a few lessons I've learned. We really have to stop treating MCPs like APIs with better descriptions. There's too big of a gap between how models interact with tools and what APIs are actually designed for. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The major difference is that developers read docs, experiment, and remember. AI models start fresh every conversation with only your tool descriptions to guide them, until they start calling tools. Then there's a big opportunity that a ton of MCP servers don't currently use: Nudging the AI in the right direction by treating responses as prompts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;One important rule is to design around &lt;strong&gt;user intent, not API endpoints.&lt;/strong&gt; I took a look at an older project of mine where I had an Agent helping out with some community management using the &lt;a href="http://Circle.so"&gt;Circle.so&lt;/a&gt; API. I basically gave it access to half the endpoints through function calling, but it never worked reliably. I dove back in thought for a bit about how I'd approach that project nowadays. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A useful usecase was getting insights into user activity. The old API-centric way would be to make the model call &lt;code&gt;get_members&lt;/code&gt;, then loop through them to call &lt;code&gt;get_member_activity&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;get_member_posts&lt;/code&gt;, etc. It's clumsy, eats tons of tokens and is error prone. The intent-based approach is to create a single &lt;code&gt;getSpaceActivity&lt;/code&gt; tool that does all of that work on the server and returns one clean, rich object.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Once you have a good intent-based tool like that, the next question is how you describe it. The model needs to know &lt;em&gt;when&lt;/em&gt; to use it, and how. I've found simple XML tags directly in the description work wonders for this, separating the &amp;quot;what it's for&amp;quot; from the &amp;quot;how to use it.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;usecase&amp;gt;Retrieves member activity for a space, including posts, comments, and last active date. Useful for tracking activity of users.&amp;lt;/usecase&amp;gt; &amp;lt;instructions&amp;gt;Returns members sorted by total activity. Includes last 30 days by default.&amp;lt;/instructions&amp;gt; &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's good to think about every response as an opportunity to prompt the model. The model has no memory of your API's flow, so you have to remind it every time. A successful response can do more than just present the data, it can also contain instructions that guides the next logical step, like &lt;code&gt;&amp;quot;Found 25 active members. Use bulkMessage() to contact them.&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is even more critical for &lt;strong&gt;errors&lt;/strong&gt;. A perfect example is the Supabase MCP. I've used it with Claude 4 Opus, and it occasionally hallucinates a &lt;code&gt;project_id&lt;/code&gt;. Whenever Claude calls a tool with a made up project_id, the MCP's response is &lt;code&gt;{&amp;quot;error&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Unauthorized&amp;quot;}&lt;/code&gt;, which is technically correct but completely unhelpful. It stops the model in its tracks because the error suggests that it doesn't have rights to take the intended action.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;An error message &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; the documentation at that moment, and it must be educational. Instead of just &amp;quot;Unauthorized,&amp;quot; a helpful response would be: &lt;code&gt;{&amp;quot;error&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Project ID 'proj_abc123' not found or you lack permissions. To see available projects, use the listProjects() tool.&amp;quot;}&lt;/code&gt; This tells the model &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; it failed and gives it a specific, actionable next step to solve the problem.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That also helps with preventing a ton of bloat in the initial prompt. If a model gets a tool call right 90+% of the time, and it occasionally makes a mistake that it can easily correct because of a good error response, then there's no need to add descriptions for every single edge case. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If anyone is interested, I wrote a longer post about it here: &lt;a href="https://useai.substack.com/p/mcp-tool-design-from-apis-to-ai-first"&gt;MCP Tool Design: From APIs to AI-First Interfaces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/sjoti"&gt; /u/sjoti &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq69b3/good_mcp_design_is_understanding_that_every_tool/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq69b3/good_mcp_design_is_understanding_that_every_tool/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lq69b3/good_mcp_design_is_understanding_that_every_tool/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-02T20:21:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1h7pl2v</id>
    <title>Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T01:23:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/BlNcrgap-6pz7IdUsbomFSVuqp_BB8tTUEFVIk6by18.jpg?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f25629e364c60f72e8d88ce33c5b1f90a326c065" title="Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/punkpeye/awesome-mcp-servers/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T01:23:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1h7qe88</id>
    <title>Join the Model Context Protocol Discord Server!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T02:04:10+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://glama.ai/mcp/discord"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7qe88/join_the_model_context_protocol_discord_server/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7qe88/join_the_model_context_protocol_discord_server/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T02:04:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
