<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>/r/mcp/.rss</id>
  <title>Model Context Protocol (MCP)</title>
  <updated>2025-07-11T23:24:11+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/" rel="alternate"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <icon>https://www.redditstatic.com/icon.png/</icon>
  <subtitle>The Model Context Protocol is an open standard that enables developers to build secure, two-way connections between their data sources and AI-powered tools</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx5lxf</id>
    <title>WaaSuP - Composer MCP</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T12:28:50+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Comptrio</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Comptrio</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WaaSuP&lt;/strong&gt; (Website as a Server unleashing Power) - A production-ready, SaaS-oriented Model Context Protocol (MCP) server implementation for PHP. Built with enterprise-grade features including OAuth 2.1 authentication, real-time Server-Sent Events (SSE), and comprehensive tool management.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Features a dedicated MCP endpoint for working with the software itself during setup or planning to add MCP to an existing website. The codebase, docs, and examples are all available to an LLM and live at seolinkmap . com/mcp-repo &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WaaSuP with your site? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/SEOLinkMap/waasup"&gt;https://github.com/SEOLinkMap/waasup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Comptrio"&gt; /u/Comptrio &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx5lxf/waasup_composer_mcp/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx5lxf/waasup_composer_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx5lxf/waasup_composer_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T12:28:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx8arw</id>
    <title>Librechat MCP SSE server in python with per-user authentication explained</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T14:26:52+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/geobali</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/geobali</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent a lot of time trying to understand how to capture MCP request headers in Python SSE MCP servers. My goal was to eventually integrate the MCP servers with LibreChat because it has a nice UI support for per-user authentication. I wanted to exclusively use the &lt;a href="https://github.com/modelcontextprotocol/python-sdk"&gt;python-skd&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I wrote a simple example using a Salesforce MCP server: there is nothing particular to Salesforce though, the code is generic. The gist of it on the python side:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;def query_salesforce(soql_query: str, ctx: Context) -&amp;gt; str: &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;Issues a REST query to salesforce Parameters ---------- soql_query : str SOQL query to execute against Salesforce Returns ------- str Markdown formatted table of results &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot; headers_info = {} if ctx.request_context.request: headers_info = dict(ctx.request_context.request.headers) salesforce_client = initialize_client(username=headers_info['x-auth-username'], ... &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;p&gt;LibreChat passes user credentials as HTTP headers based on your &lt;code&gt;librechat.yaml&lt;/code&gt; config. Users enter creds once in the UI, then every MCP request includes them automatically.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Full writeup with code: &lt;a href="https://balikasg.github.io/python/Librechat/"&gt;https://balikasg.github.io/python/Librechat/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/geobali"&gt; /u/geobali &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx8arw/librechat_mcp_sse_server_in_python_with_peruser/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx8arw/librechat_mcp_sse_server_in_python_with_peruser/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx8arw/librechat_mcp_sse_server_in_python_with_peruser/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T14:26:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxahlo</id>
    <title>Voice Mode MCP - Conversational Coding</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T15:53:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/mike-bailey</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/mike-bailey</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voice Mode MCP enables natural voice conversations with LLMs. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Voice Coding while walking the dog, cleaning the house or even having a bath creates more productive time - something most of us could use more of.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Installing Voice Mode MCP on Claude Code can be a game changer for developers. This free and open source solution allows natural conversations, without having to look at the screen or use the keyboard.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It defaults to locally hosted open source models for speech recognition and Text to Speech if detected and falls back to OpenAI API (required OpenAI API Key).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://getvoicemode.com"&gt;https://getvoicemode.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/y07nFEk9Q6M"&gt;https://youtu.be/y07nFEk9Q6M&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/mike-bailey"&gt; /u/mike-bailey &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxahlo/voice_mode_mcp_conversational_coding/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxahlo/voice_mode_mcp_conversational_coding/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxahlo/voice_mode_mcp_conversational_coding/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T15:53:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxajpp</id>
    <title>You can now bundle multiple MCP server actions (Supabase+Jira) into a single MCP server in seconds</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T15:55:54+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/SunilKumarDash</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/SunilKumarDash</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most significant pain points I felt with the current MCP servers is that the tools are rigid. If you add a Supabase MCP, you have to use whatever is provided with the server; no way to select specific tools. If you had to use another server like Jira, you would have to add another MCP server with another set of unwanted tools. Filling up the model context and reducing tool call reliability.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is something I believe a lot of people wanted. And you can get all these things on Composio MCP dashboard&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Select an MCP server and choose specific actions you need&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;If you need more servers, select and add the actions&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bundle the Server actions into one with a single HTTP URL.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Add it to the clients and use only the selected ones.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;This also significantly reduces the surface area for any kind of accidents related to LLMs accessing endpoints they shouldn't and also leaves space for precise tool calls.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Check this blog post where I have used Suapabase and Jira together in a single server: &lt;a href="https://composio.dev/blog/how-to-use-supabase-and-jira-mcp-with-cursor-to-improve-productivity"&gt;Supabase and Jira MCP in Cursor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Would love your thoughts on it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/SunilKumarDash"&gt; /u/SunilKumarDash &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxajpp/you_can_now_bundle_multiple_mcp_server_actions/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxajpp/you_can_now_bundle_multiple_mcp_server_actions/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxajpp/you_can_now_bundle_multiple_mcp_server_actions/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T15:55:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lwj3o8</id>
    <title>Try MCP Toolbox for Databases by Google today!</title>
    <updated>2025-07-10T17:44:09+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/KlutzyPangolin2378</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/KlutzyPangolin2378</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;🧰 🚀Extremely excited to share that MCP Toolbox for Databases as #3 on the GitHub trending (&lt;a href="https://github.com/trending"&gt;https://github.com/trending&lt;/a&gt;) list today! We've seen a pretty big explosion in interest over the last few days! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Toolbox takes a different approach to many MCP database servers, giving you a lot of flexibility and control on both what and how your data is exposed to your LLM. Not only that, but Toolbox works with more than 17 different database engines (with more on the way)!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to do more with your database, come check us out! Toolbox works out of the box with MCP, supercharging your developer workflows (such as with #GeminiCLI or Cursor): &lt;a href="https://medium.com/google-cloud/leverage-bigquerys-analytical-prowess-with-the-gemini-cli-and-mcp-toolbox-part-1-d4bcdf1a31bf"&gt;https://medium.com/google-cloud/leverage-bigquerys-analytical-prowess-with-the-gemini-cli-and-mcp-toolbox-part-1-d4bcdf1a31bf&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We also have specialized SDKs for Python, JS, and Go that provide an MCP-like experience with extra security and performance! They work directly with your favorite frameworks -- including #ADK, #LangChain, and #Genkit! Python: &lt;a href="https://github.com/googleapis/mcp-toolbox-sdk-python"&gt;https://github.com/googleapis/mcp-toolbox-sdk-python&lt;/a&gt; Javascript​: &lt;a href="https://github.com/googleapis/mcp-toolbox-sdk-js"&gt;https://github.com/googleapis/mcp-toolbox-sdk-js&lt;/a&gt; Go: &lt;a href="https://github.com/googleapis/mcp-toolbox-sdk-go"&gt;https://github.com/googleapis/mcp-toolbox-sdk-go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/KlutzyPangolin2378"&gt; /u/KlutzyPangolin2378 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lwj3o8/try_mcp_toolbox_for_databases_by_google_today/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lwj3o8/try_mcp_toolbox_for_databases_by_google_today/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lwj3o8/try_mcp_toolbox_for_databases_by_google_today/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-10T17:44:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lwony0</id>
    <title>Spent 6 months architecting this fintech beast - roast my system design 🔥</title>
    <updated>2025-07-10T21:23:13+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Nipurn_1234</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Nipurn_1234</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lwony0/spent_6_months_architecting_this_fintech_beast/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Spent 6 months architecting this fintech beast - roast my system design 🔥" src="https://preview.redd.it/za4073d364cf1.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=82bbcf2e4e06fc537e379cacb77cb494bda90df6" title="Spent 6 months architecting this fintech beast - roast my system design 🔥" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is my take on a modern financial services platform architecture that I've been working on. It includes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- AI-powered trading and risk management&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Multi-channel customer experience (web, mobile, chatbot)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Real-time financial data processing&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Compliance and regulatory reporting&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Cloud-native infrastructure with monitoring&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I know the diagram is dense AF, but I wanted to show the full picture. The system handles everything from customer onboarding to complex financial operations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Looking for honest feedback - especially on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Are there any critical components I'm missing?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Is this overengineered for what it does?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- How would you simplify this without losing functionality?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Any obvious security or scalability red flags?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Don't hold back - I need to know if this will actually work in production or if I've created a beautiful disaster 😅&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Nipurn_1234"&gt; /u/Nipurn_1234 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.redd.it/za4073d364cf1.png"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lwony0/spent_6_months_architecting_this_fintech_beast/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lwony0/spent_6_months_architecting_this_fintech_beast/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-10T21:23:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx75tk</id>
    <title>LLM following instructions from mcp server</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T13:38:59+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/AccordingDoughnut903</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/AccordingDoughnut903</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi i am building a mcp as a side project, idea is to build mcp for a financial audit, so it involves multi step logic: 1. Asking for specific financial documents (pdf, csv, excel) 2. cross referencing these documents this involves filtering and matching tables 3. After we cross reference tables we need to look for the references in the pdfs and verify the records (model needs to do this). 4. As a last step model has to create a new humanly readable table and return it in the chat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To achieve this i am using python sdk with open-webui ( forked and modified with fielupload widget which is rendered after llm calls tool and tool returns json which is parsed and provides details to the widget.) for models i use ollama/open router. for serving mcp over http i use mcpo.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Problem that i face is following: as the processing is multistep i need to provide the instructions to the model on how and when to use the tools. Even though llm is calling create widget mcp correctly it is not following instructions to display returned json at the end of the response, i think that maybe model is not paying attention to the instruction given by mcp because if i change the system prompt and describe how to properly use the tools im the system prompt it is doing it without any problem but after i remove it and only place it in the description of the mcp models results are consistently bad. As i am not sure about what the problem is i think that i am doing something wrong which i dont understand. I would appreciate if you could help me here. You can ask me additional questions, i hope i wrote everything clearly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/AccordingDoughnut903"&gt; /u/AccordingDoughnut903 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx75tk/llm_following_instructions_from_mcp_server/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx75tk/llm_following_instructions_from_mcp_server/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx75tk/llm_following_instructions_from_mcp_server/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T13:38:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx4od6</id>
    <title>Trying to wrap my head around some things</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T11:41:56+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/National-Ad-1314</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/National-Ad-1314</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I've been trying to learn how to make MCP servers and work different integrations into it. Guess my goal is to just understand how it all works to then be able to work with whatever AI agents or llm tools appear in the coming years. I'm a freshly graduated software dev so alth&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We have the host which is our computer and environment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We have the client which is our ide. Most resources go into claude code here I don't use claude code or pay for the 100-200 subscription so I tend to use vscode with augment as my agent. Augment also has some built in MCP.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Where I start getting a bit overwhelmed is the server. So we can spin out a local server. We can also make a tunnel to allow this server to be called from outside our network and if we host it then it can be used. But then there's 1000s of other MCP servers. At this point there's crickets in my brain trying to figure out how to make agentic applications with MCP. Do I even need my own server? Is this like making an API when I have nothing I even want to share? Do I just need to bring external mcps into my client to make an application that does anything worthwhile?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I've done the hugging face course where you make a PR agent that through webhooks with GitHub actions let's your MCP reply to you with information in terminal. They have further examples where you integrate slack messages. But then GitHub and slack have their own MCP servers. I just don't get what gets implemented where even though the thing I built in the course worked. Where do external mcp servers play a role and where do you just need your MCP servers with API calls?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tldr; when do you need your own server. When do you just need something to call in every external server ?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/National-Ad-1314"&gt; /u/National-Ad-1314 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx4od6/trying_to_wrap_my_head_around_some_things/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx4od6/trying_to_wrap_my_head_around_some_things/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx4od6/trying_to_wrap_my_head_around_some_things/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T11:41:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxdfwv</id>
    <title>Developing an MCP system</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T17:47:45+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Competitive_Crew_686</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Competitive_Crew_686</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxdfwv/developing_an_mcp_system/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Developing an MCP system" src="https://a.thumbs.redditmedia.com/Uww-oSRbbKftZNsFwPt5CDd2SuLQ5aCHYXM-Ra9Umj8.jpg" title="Developing an MCP system" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;hey y'all ,i'm tryna build this sort of architecture for an MCP (Model Context Protocol) system.&lt;br /&gt; not sure how doable it really is ,is it challenging in practice?&lt;br /&gt; any recommendations, maybe open-source projects or github repos that do something similar&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://preview.redd.it/a8jpze819acf1.png?width=646&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a109ee0466a2b0e7aa719f2bebe8226ddb322ca8"&gt;https://preview.redd.it/a8jpze819acf1.png?width=646&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a109ee0466a2b0e7aa719f2bebe8226ddb322ca8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://preview.redd.it/ppxupkf09acf1.png?width=1226&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1d1332f27b72c1f2f210337a138f574036af772c"&gt;https://preview.redd.it/ppxupkf09acf1.png?width=1226&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1d1332f27b72c1f2f210337a138f574036af772c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Competitive_Crew_686"&gt; /u/Competitive_Crew_686 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxdfwv/developing_an_mcp_system/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxdfwv/developing_an_mcp_system/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxdfwv/developing_an_mcp_system/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T17:47:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxfsx3</id>
    <title>MCP-Server that CREATES designs in Figma / Penpot / etc?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T19:20:33+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Sir_Alex_Senior</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Sir_Alex_Senior</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;is there a MCP-Server that creates designs in Tools like Figma?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Until now i just saw MCPs that read design from Figma and then create code.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Alex&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Sir_Alex_Senior"&gt; /u/Sir_Alex_Senior &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxfsx3/mcpserver_that_creates_designs_in_figma_penpot_etc/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxfsx3/mcpserver_that_creates_designs_in_figma_penpot_etc/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxfsx3/mcpserver_that_creates_designs_in_figma_penpot_etc/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T19:20:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxg4qx</id>
    <title>I am still confused on the difference between Model Context Protocol vs Tool Calling (Function Calling); What are the limitations and boundaries of both?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T19:33:48+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Edsaur</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Edsaur</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the things I grasp between both please correct me if I have not fully understood them well, I am still confused since these two are new to me:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Function Calling (tool calling), the LLM could quickly access them based on what the context we gave the LLM for example I have a function for getting the best restaurants around my area, that could get the restaurant from either an api GET endpoint or defined items in that function and that would be the one that LLM will use as a response back to the user. Additionally, with tool calling the tools are defined with-in the app itself thus codes for tool calling must be hardcoded and live in one app.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;With MCPs on the other hand, we leverage on using tools that lives on a different MCP Servers that we could use using the MCP Client. Now tools that we leverage on MCPs are much powerful than those of tool calling since we can let the LLM do stuffs for us right or can function calling do that as well? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then based on my understanding is that the LLM see them both as schemas only, right?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now with those, what are their limitations and boundaries?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And these are my other questions also:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Why was MCP created in the first place? How does it replace Tool Calling?&lt;br /&gt; 2. What problems MCP answer that Tool Calling does not?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please add another valuable knowledge that I could learn about these two technologies.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Edsaur"&gt; /u/Edsaur &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxg4qx/i_am_still_confused_on_the_difference_between/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxg4qx/i_am_still_confused_on_the_difference_between/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxg4qx/i_am_still_confused_on_the_difference_between/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T19:33:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxhrnz</id>
    <title>Just published a full walkthrough on getting started with .dxt extensions in Claude Desktop. Covers manifest setup, packaging, and integration.</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T20:40:13+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/No-Abies7108</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/No-Abies7108</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxhrnz/just_published_a_full_walkthrough_on_getting/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Just published a full walkthrough on getting started with .dxt extensions in Claude Desktop. Covers manifest setup, packaging, and integration." src="https://preview.redd.it/fb0938co3bcf1.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c3f67e49d8ae789bb8058d83a4ab7b5966eb4a2b" title="Just published a full walkthrough on getting started with .dxt extensions in Claude Desktop. Covers manifest setup, packaging, and integration." /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href="https://glama.ai/blog/2025-07-11-getting-started-with-mcp-desktop-extensions-dxt-in-claude-desktop"&gt;https://glama.ai/blog/2025-07-11-getting-started-with-mcp-desktop-extensions-dxt-in-claude-desktop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/No-Abies7108"&gt; /u/No-Abies7108 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.redd.it/fb0938co3bcf1.png"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxhrnz/just_published_a_full_walkthrough_on_getting/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxhrnz/just_published_a_full_walkthrough_on_getting/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T20:40:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx901k</id>
    <title>S&amp;P Global's Next in Tech Podcast - Episode on MCP Security</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T14:55:45+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Agile_Breakfast4261</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Agile_Breakfast4261</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Very neat podcast on MCP security issues from S&amp;amp;P Global.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the podcast they cover the main security risks, some of the missteps so far, the pressure to move forward with MCP adoption despite these risks, and what work is now being done now to make MCPs more secure - including steps to move beyond an 0Auth-based approach.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you're not up to speed on all the MCP security risks this is a nice primer. I don't feel they covered everything - but then the episode is only 30 minutes long!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you listened - what did you learn/what did you think they got wrong or could've covered differently?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Personally I feel there could have been more emphasis on potential solutions, or maybe they could cover security risks and emerging solutions/strategies to those risks in separate episodes?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links to listen:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spglobal.com/market-intelligence/en/news-insights/podcasts/next-in-tech/next-in-tech-ep-225-security-for-mcp"&gt;https://www.spglobal.com/market-intelligence/en/news-insights/podcasts/next-in-tech/next-in-tech-ep-225-security-for-mcp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TZ_WWrRZtM0"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TZ_WWrRZtM0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The previous episode of their podcast also covered the basics of MCPs. I think most people in this community will be up to speed with all the MCP basics already, but here's that episode too if you're interested:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spglobal.com/market-intelligence/en/news-insights/podcasts/next-in-tech/next-in-tech-ep-224-context-around-mcp"&gt;https://www.spglobal.com/market-intelligence/en/news-insights/podcasts/next-in-tech/next-in-tech-ep-224-context-around-mcp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Agile_Breakfast4261"&gt; /u/Agile_Breakfast4261 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx901k/sp_globals_next_in_tech_podcast_episode_on_mcp/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx901k/sp_globals_next_in_tech_podcast_episode_on_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx901k/sp_globals_next_in_tech_podcast_episode_on_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T14:55:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxidn5</id>
    <title>MCP infrastructure running on Cloudflare Worker</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T21:04:59+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Neurabase</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Neurabase</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxidn5/mcp_infrastructure_running_on_cloudflare_worker/"&gt; &lt;img alt="MCP infrastructure running on Cloudflare Worker" src="https://preview.redd.it/w2a2a9zy7bcf1.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5ad5e12b89b04d4e6ff2fe5689da3468d6d405b3" title="MCP infrastructure running on Cloudflare Worker" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey 👋 &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am currently experimenting and building &lt;a href="https://neurabase.deploya.dev"&gt;Neurabase&lt;/a&gt; as a proof of concept to run all MCP servers on Cloudflare Workers infrastructure and using the power of CDN to deliver stability, speed and scalability. &lt;strong&gt;It's running smooth as butter, one button click and you are up and running in your Cursor editor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Would love to have your feedback of what can be improved.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Neurabase"&gt; /u/Neurabase &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.redd.it/w2a2a9zy7bcf1.png"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxidn5/mcp_infrastructure_running_on_cloudflare_worker/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxidn5/mcp_infrastructure_running_on_cloudflare_worker/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T21:04:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx1woz</id>
    <title>I built the first MCP client to support Elicitation (open source)</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T08:52:06+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/matt8p</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/matt8p</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx1woz/i_built_the_first_mcp_client_to_support/"&gt; &lt;img alt="I built the first MCP client to support Elicitation (open source)" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/ZDRsMzhndDJsN2NmMd4iMYm6NV4MSvbYWkC4mLMJT0UuI_lqe3Szad02Un9U.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=96d8ce2c6dca949ce895f2b0aa7fcbf23e02b0c6" title="I built the first MCP client to support Elicitation (open source)" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey y’all, I’m Matt. I maintain the MCPJam inspector. It’s an open source tool to test and debug MCP servers. I am so excited to announce that we built support for elicitation, and proud that we're one of the first to support it. Now you can test your elicitation implementation in your server.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Test individual tools for elicitation (demo 0:00 - 0:10)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Test elicitation against an LLM in our LLM playground. We support Claude, OpenAI, and Ollama models. (0:15 - 0:28) &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wanted to thank this community for helping drive this project. Shout out @osojukumari and @ignaciocossio.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you like this project or want to try it out, please check out our repo and consider giving it a star!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/MCPJam/inspector"&gt;https://github.com/MCPJam/inspector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/matt8p"&gt; /u/matt8p &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://v.redd.it/w1sedgt2l7cf1"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx1woz/i_built_the_first_mcp_client_to_support/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx1woz/i_built_the_first_mcp_client_to_support/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T08:52:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxj37f</id>
    <title>Marketing agent</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T21:34:27+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Ok-Wealth5360</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Ok-Wealth5360</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to build and MCP marketing ai agent Which should generate a marketing strategy and its posts and videos content and to post that on social media platform then to monitor and learn from it to adjust accordingly and for future strategies.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I want to know the best way to finish this project asap because it is for university.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Ok-Wealth5360"&gt; /u/Ok-Wealth5360 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxj37f/marketing_agent/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxj37f/marketing_agent/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxj37f/marketing_agent/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T21:34:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx3ykn</id>
    <title>How to create and deploy a new MCP server anywhere in less than 2 minutes</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T11:02:36+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/phuctm97</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/phuctm97</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx3ykn/how_to_create_and_deploy_a_new_mcp_server/"&gt; &lt;img alt="How to create and deploy a new MCP server anywhere in less than 2 minutes" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/MXpxdjF3cnQ3OGNmMXGwedDh5ssIn0MLHsupTYQfSbCTQtWK0iw0sdwgjG99.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ed79e26a4a05eeb92397313f19116159541437ef" title="How to create and deploy a new MCP server anywhere in less than 2 minutes" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey MCP nerds, just want to share with you how I can create and deploy a new MCP server anywhere TypeScript/JavaScript runs in less than 2 minutes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I used an open-source tool called &lt;a href="https://modelfetch.com"&gt;ModelFetch&lt;/a&gt;, which helps scaffold and connect my MCP servers to many TypeScript/JavaScript runtimes: Node.js, Bun, Deno, Vercel, Cloudflare, AWS Lambda, and more coming.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The MCP server is built with the &lt;a href="https://github.com/modelcontextprotocol/typescript-sdk"&gt;official MCP TypeScript SDK&lt;/a&gt; so there is no new API to learn and your server will work with many transports &amp;amp; tools that already support the official SDK.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spoiler: I'm the creator of the open-source library ModelFetch&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/phuctm97"&gt; /u/phuctm97 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://v.redd.it/4xyeuvrt78cf1"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx3ykn/how_to_create_and_deploy_a_new_mcp_server/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx3ykn/how_to_create_and_deploy_a_new_mcp_server/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T11:02:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxk3kj</id>
    <title>Best source for API schemas for MCP command hookup?</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T22:17:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/After-Kick-9574</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/After-Kick-9574</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We (Vendia) are looking at expanding our support for existing enterprise APIs in MCP. To do that effectively (and programmatically), we need to solve for 3 things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Catalog -- where/how to locate APIs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Schemas -- programmatically discovering and conveying/converting parameter and result types into MCP-compatible formats&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Authentication/invocation -- enabling MCP clients to successfully execute the actual API invocations&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;Looking for feedback on the first two in particular in terms of what (especially enterprise) developers would like to see supported. For example, we could mine an existing API management or gateway service, such as Google Apigee or Amazon API Gateway. Or we could make the catalog aspect manual (i.e., you have to list each API to solve for #1) but then accept a formalism like OpenAPI or gRCP for #2 to avoid the need to &amp;quot;code&amp;quot; each API's type. Feedback appreciated as replies or DMs -- for the APIs you'd like to see connected as MCP commands, what would offer the best compromise around ease of use, automation, long-term maintenance, and control?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/After-Kick-9574"&gt; /u/After-Kick-9574 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxk3kj/best_source_for_api_schemas_for_mcp_command_hookup/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxk3kj/best_source_for_api_schemas_for_mcp_command_hookup/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxk3kj/best_source_for_api_schemas_for_mcp_command_hookup/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T22:17:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxfkqk</id>
    <title>How to utilise other primitives like resources so that other clients can consume them</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T19:11:31+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/caksters</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/caksters</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;My team is building an internal MCP server that’s currently consumed by our own agentic MCP client. So far, everything works as expected.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The server exposes a single generic tool that allows the agent to fetch relevant data and generate analytics based on the user’s query. The challenge is that under the hood, this tool can hit many different internal endpoints — but which one to use depends entirely on the context of the user’s query.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To solve this, we’ve been trying to figure out how to guide the LLM toward the correct endpoint behind that generic tool. In our client, we’re experimenting with dynamically modifying the system prompt to inject relevant resource hints or instructions, based on the user’s intent. But this creates a tight coupling between our MCP client and server — the logic for query interpretation and resource mapping lives entirely in the client.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now we’re exploring whether MCP resources could help us here — by making each endpoint or dataset its own named resource, we could expose that through the server and let the client fetch and present those to the LLM. But again, the problem is that this behavior (using the resources to enrich the prompt or guide the LLM) would be specific to our client implementation. If another MCP client like Claude Desktop connects to our server, it wouldn’t know that it needs to inject this resource-based context, since it treats everything based on its own assumptions about tool invocation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So we’re stuck with a generic tool that technically works, but no good way to expose usage guidance to external clients in a standardized, client-agnostic way. Curious if anyone else has faced this issue — especially when trying to decouple server-side logic from how prompts are constructed or interpreted by different clients.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/caksters"&gt; /u/caksters &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxfkqk/how_to_utilise_other_primitives_like_resources_so/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxfkqk/how_to_utilise_other_primitives_like_resources_so/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxfkqk/how_to_utilise_other_primitives_like_resources_so/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T19:11:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx3djy</id>
    <title>oauth + mcp: a few things i wish i did right the first time</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T10:27:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/KafkaaTamura_</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/KafkaaTamura_</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;if you're securing a private MCP, the basics are fine, but the edge cases sneak up fast. here are 3 things that saved me pain:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;don’t validate tokens inside the model server&lt;/strong&gt; run everything through a lightweight proxy that handles auth: jwt validation, scopes, tenant mapping, all of it. keeps your mcp logic clean + stateless.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;treat scopes as billing units&lt;/strong&gt; scopes like &lt;code&gt;read.4k&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;write.unlimited&lt;/code&gt;, etc. make it way easier to map usage to pricing later.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rotate client secrets like api keys&lt;/strong&gt; most people set and forget these. build rotation + revocation in early.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;shameless plug but working on a platform that does all of this (handling oauth, usage tracking, billing etc for MCP servers) for FREE. if you're building something and tired of hacking this stuff together, sign up for early beta. i spent way too much time building the tool instead of a pretty landing page lmao so here's a crappy google form to make do. thanks. &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/sxEhw5WqMYdKeNvUA"&gt;https://forms.gle/sxEhw5WqMYdKeNvUA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/KafkaaTamura_"&gt; /u/KafkaaTamura_ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx3djy/oauth_mcp_a_few_things_i_wish_i_did_right_the/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx3djy/oauth_mcp_a_few_things_i_wish_i_did_right_the/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx3djy/oauth_mcp_a_few_things_i_wish_i_did_right_the/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T10:27:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxhf6a</id>
    <title>An alternative to semantic or benchmark-based routing: A fast preference-aligned routing model</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T20:26:08+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/AdditionalWeb107</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/AdditionalWeb107</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxhf6a/an_alternative_to_semantic_or_benchmarkbased/"&gt; &lt;img alt="An alternative to semantic or benchmark-based routing: A fast preference-aligned routing model" src="https://preview.redd.it/rtik28n11bcf1.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bae324cd1569468056afec8fe2277a749be739a7" title="An alternative to semantic or benchmark-based routing: A fast preference-aligned routing model" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I am one of the core maintainers of &lt;a href="https://github.com/katanemo/archgw"&gt;Arch&lt;/a&gt; - an open-source distributed proxy for agents written in Rust. A few days ago we launched &lt;a href="https://huggingface.co/katanemo/Arch-Router-1.5B"&gt;Arch-Router&lt;/a&gt; on HuggingFace, a 1.5B router model designed for preference-aligned routing (and of course integrated in the proxy server). Full paper: &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.16655"&gt;https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.16655&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As teams integrate multiple LLMs - each with different strengths, styles, or cost/latency profiles — routing the right prompt to the right model becomes a critical part of the application design. But it’s still an open problem. Existing routing systems fall into two camps:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embedding-based or semantic routers&lt;/strong&gt; map the user’s prompt to a dense vector and route based on similarity — but they struggle in practice: they lack context awareness (so follow-ups like “And Boston?” are misrouted), fail to detect negation or logic (“I don’t want a refund” vs. “I want a refund”), miss rare or emerging intents that don’t form clear clusters, and can’t handle short, vague queries like “cancel” without added context.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance-based routers&lt;/strong&gt; pick models based on benchmarks like MMLU or MT-Bench, or based on latency or cost curves. But benchmarks often miss what matters in production: domain-specific quality or subjective preferences especially as developers evaluate the effectiveness of their prompts against selected models.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Arch-Router takes a different approach: route by preferences written in plain language. You write rules like “contract clauses → GPT-4o” or “quick travel tips → Gemini Flash.” The router maps the prompt (and conversation context) to those rules using a lightweight 1.5B autoregressive model. No retraining, no fragile if/else chains. We built this with input from teams at Twilio and Atlassian. It handles intent drift, supports multi-turn conversations, and lets you swap in or out models with a one-line change to the routing policy. Full details are in our &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.16655"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;, but here’s a snapshot:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Specs:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;1.5B parameters — runs on a single GPU (or CPU for testing)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;No retraining needed — point it at any mix of LLMs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Outperforms larger closed models on conversational routing benchmarks (details in the paper)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoy the paper, the model and the usage integrated via the proxy&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/AdditionalWeb107"&gt; /u/AdditionalWeb107 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.redd.it/rtik28n11bcf1.png"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxhf6a/an_alternative_to_semantic_or_benchmarkbased/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxhf6a/an_alternative_to_semantic_or_benchmarkbased/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T20:26:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxl30n</id>
    <title>Voice Mode for Claude Code! (Easy Install)</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T23:01:30+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/johnmatthewtennant</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/johnmatthewtennant</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxl30n/voice_mode_for_claude_code_easy_install/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Voice Mode for Claude Code! (Easy Install)" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/jOngs_13XnqAemet6maLa-0X3_gT84L1ENmePcgIeFY.jpeg?width=320&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a49789c6bbfb9e1f509a220b4fea58e0a67f4e13" title="Voice Mode for Claude Code! (Easy Install)" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/johnmatthewtennant"&gt; /u/johnmatthewtennant &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/GbDatJtm8_k"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxl30n/voice_mode_for_claude_code_easy_install/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxl30n/voice_mode_for_claude_code_easy_install/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T23:01:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxduxr</id>
    <title>Spent the last few weeks building this open source framework for MCP servers - DyneMCP</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T18:03:46+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Feeling-Stop-897</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Feeling-Stop-897</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was building a bunch of Model Context Protocol servers for different projects and kept copy-pasting the same boilerplate over and over. Got sick of it real quick lol. Decided to bite the bullet and build &lt;strong&gt;DyneMCP&lt;/strong&gt; - basically a framework that handles all the boring stuff so you can focus on the actual logic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What it does:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;One command setup (no joke, literally &lt;code&gt;pnpm dlx @ /dynemcp/create-dynemcp my-project&lt;/code&gt; and you're good)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Comes with templates for different use cases&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Security stuff baked in (learned this the hard way)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;TypeScript&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Actually production ready (unlike my usual weekend projects 😅)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Been using it for my own stuff and it's been solid. Thought maybe others dealing with MCP might find it useful too.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Would love to hear what you think! Also open to contributions if anyone's interested. Still got a bunch of ideas for v2 but wanted to get this out there first.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Feeling-Stop-897"&gt; /u/Feeling-Stop-897 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxduxr/spent_the_last_few_weeks_building_this_open/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxduxr/spent_the_last_few_weeks_building_this_open/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxduxr/spent_the_last_few_weeks_building_this_open/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T18:03:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lx8cs0</id>
    <title>Open Source MCP</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T14:29:09+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/Middle_Finish4234</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/Middle_Finish4234</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m currently working on an MCP project for my internship and it really opened my eyes to the capabilities of this protocol. I want to keep getting involved and learn more but I’ve never been good enough to get a project going and have an end to end product. Are there any open source MCP related projects or would anyone be willing to work on one with me? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I guess a little background, I work in security and I’m very interested in the concept of AI within the security space.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/Middle_Finish4234"&gt; /u/Middle_Finish4234 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx8cs0/open_source_mcp/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx8cs0/open_source_mcp/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lx8cs0/open_source_mcp/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T14:29:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1lxg10q</id>
    <title>The simplest way to use MCP. All local, 100% open source.</title>
    <updated>2025-07-11T19:29:43+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/squirrelEgg</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/squirrelEgg</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxg10q/the_simplest_way_to_use_mcp_all_local_100_open/"&gt; &lt;img alt="The simplest way to use MCP. All local, 100% open source." src="https://external-preview.redd.it/MWpyM2d3MnZwYWNmMddMlsp_yQ3B-p5J3I45oUH3GS_pyPG30IGFJ_76-Zu_.png?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=44b92c16f9ad50c473ed13ef7874778f9bfd793d" title="The simplest way to use MCP. All local, 100% open source." /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class="md"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello &lt;a href="/r/mcp"&gt;r/mcp&lt;/a&gt;. Just wanted to show you something we've been hacking on: a fully open source, local first MCP gateway that allows you to connect Claude, Cursor or VSCode to any MCP server in 30 seconds.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can check it out at &lt;a href="https://director.run"&gt;https://director.run&lt;/a&gt; or star the repo here: &lt;a href="https://github.com/director-run/director"&gt;https://github.com/director-run/director&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is a super early version, but it's stable and would love feedback from the community. There's a lot we still want to build: tool filtering, oauth, middleware etc. But thought it's time to share! Would love it if you could try it out and let us know what you think. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/squirrelEgg"&gt; /u/squirrelEgg &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://v.redd.it/reqebw2vpacf1"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxg10q/the_simplest_way_to_use_mcp_all_local_100_open/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1lxg10q/the_simplest_way_to_use_mcp_all_local_100_open/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2025-07-11T19:29:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1h7pl2v</id>
    <title>Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T01:23:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"&gt; &lt;img alt="Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers" src="https://external-preview.redd.it/BlNcrgap-6pz7IdUsbomFSVuqp_BB8tTUEFVIk6by18.jpg?width=640&amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f25629e364c60f72e8d88ce33c5b1f90a326c065" title="Awesome MCP Servers – A curated list of awesome Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/punkpeye/awesome-mcp-servers/"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7pl2v/awesome_mcp_servers_a_curated_list_of_awesome/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T01:23:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>t3_1h7qe88</id>
    <title>Join the Model Context Protocol Discord Server!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T02:04:10+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>/u/punkpeye</name>
      <uri>https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"&gt; /u/punkpeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://glama.ai/mcp/discord"&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7qe88/join_the_model_context_protocol_discord_server/"&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/mcp/comments/1h7qe88/join_the_model_context_protocol_discord_server/"/>
    <category term="mcp" label="r/mcp"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T02:04:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
